<SAMI>
<HEAD>
<HEAD>
<TITLE></TITLE>
<STYLE TYPE="text/css">
<!--
P { margin-left:8pt; margin-right:8pt; margin-bottom:2pt; margin-top:2pt;
    text-align:center;
    font-size:20pt; font-family:arial, sans-serif; font-weight:normal; color:white; }
.ENCC { Name:English; lang:en-US; SAMIType:CC;}
#STDPrn { Name:Standard Print;}
#LargePrn { Name:Large Print; font-size:25pt;}
#SmallPrn { Name:Small Print; font-size:15pt;}
-->
</STYLE>
</HEAD>
<BODY>
<SYNC Start=7273><P Class=ENCC>
It says the ignition switch fuse
<SYNC Start=10609><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=10611><P Class=ENCC>
is found at location number 27.
<SYNC Start=12411><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=12413><P Class=ENCC>
All right, 27. I need to know where that is.
<SYNC Start=14480><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=16150><P Class=ENCC>
Um, right here.
<SYNC Start=19118><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=19120><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah, okay, this one's blown.
<SYNC Start=21353><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=21355><P Class=ENCC>
What's this one, the red one?
<SYNC Start=22788><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=26761><P Class=ENCC>
Mom, dad, we got to go.
<SYNC Start=28694><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=28696><P Class=ENCC>
- Come on, come on.<br>- We see them.
<SYNC Start=31163><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=31165><P Class=ENCC>
Just need to find a fuse<br>so we can start the car.
<SYNC Start=33399><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=33401><P Class=ENCC>
Almost got it, honey. Location six.
<SYNC Start=35367><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=35369><P Class=ENCC>
That's turn signal lamps and stop lamps.
<SYNC Start=37636><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=37638><P Class=ENCC>
All right, we can live without turn signals.
<SYNC Start=39538><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=39540><P Class=ENCC>
Dad, they're com--
<SYNC Start=41306><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=382648><P Class=ENCC>
celery soup.
<SYNC Start=384049><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=384051><P Class=ENCC>
It's been here since the start.
<SYNC Start=385817><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=385819><P Class=ENCC>
You're very brave.
<SYNC Start=387753><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=387755><P Class=ENCC>
Well, I'm hoping the paprika will mask
<SYNC Start=389588><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=389590><P Class=ENCC>
the soup's celeryness.
<SYNC Start=391556><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=391558><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Then you'd be stuck with something</i>
<SYNC Start=392891><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=392893><P Class=ENCC>
<i>that tastes like paprika.</i>
<SYNC Start=394993><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=394995><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Well, I just figured since we're<br>running low on staples,</i>
<SYNC Start=398830><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=398832><P Class=ENCC>
I'd try to use a few things<br>nobody seems to want.
<SYNC Start=402167><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=403870><P Class=ENCC>
I used to make ed these<br>spring cleaning casseroles
<SYNC Start=406671><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=406673><P Class=ENCC>
just to empty the pantry.
<SYNC Start=409875><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=409877><P Class=ENCC>
I made some miracles happen<br>with water chestnuts.
<SYNC Start=412611><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=412613><P Class=ENCC>
Talk about miracles,<br>that recipe for cola canned ham.
<SYNC Start=416648><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=416650><P Class=ENCC>
Mmm.
<SYNC Start=418150><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=418152><P Class=ENCC>
Ms. peletier, you are an<br>honest to goodness hero.
<SYNC Start=421686><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=424891><P Class=ENCC>
Ugh.
<SYNC Start=426124><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=426126><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Something wrong, Shelly?</i>
<SYNC Start=427993><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=427995><P Class=ENCC>
It's just those old noodles.
<SYNC Start=431163><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=431165><P Class=ENCC>
I mean, I tell you, if someone would<br>just find me one of those machines,
<SYNC Start=434933><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=434935><P Class=ENCC>
I swear we would all be eating<br>like we were on a tour of Tuscany.
<SYNC Start=438904><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=441507><P Class=ENCC>
You know, shel, i could teach you
<SYNC Start=442941><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=442943><P Class=ENCC>
how to make pasta with your own two hands.
<SYNC Start=445744><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=445746><P Class=ENCC>
But you'd have to promise<br>not to smoke in the house.
<SYNC Start=448447><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=448449><P Class=ENCC>
It's just a disgusting habit.
<SYNC Start=450182><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=450184><P Class=ENCC>
And it kills you.
<SYNC Start=452617><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=452619><P Class=ENCC>
If you ask me, there are too many things
<SYNC Start=454553><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=454555><P Class=ENCC>
trying to do that already, right?
<SYNC Start=456555><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=458191><P Class=ENCC>
Right.
<SYNC Start=460025><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=466566><P Class=ENCC>
Your dad used to hit you and<br>then he got himself killed.
<SYNC Start=470569><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=471237><P Class=ENCC>
It happened. Now it's done.
<SYNC Start=475040><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=475042><P Class=ENCC>
You live with it or it eats you up.
<SYNC Start=477809><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=477811><P Class=ENCC>
Go home.
<SYNC Start=479778><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=498664><P Class=ENCC>
Ron.
<SYNC Start=500232><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=505872><P Class=ENCC>
Ron.
<SYNC Start=508039><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=508041><P Class=ENCC>
Can you come down here?
<SYNC Start=510175><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=524791><P Class=ENCC>
- Ron. - No, I don't want a haircut.
<SYNC Start=528627><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=529729><P Class=ENCC>
Look, I just gave myself one.
<SYNC Start=531997><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=531999><P Class=ENCC>
All right? It's all set up.
<SYNC Start=533031><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=533033><P Class=ENCC>
Don't make me do it again next week.
<SYNC Start=535233><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=535235><P Class=ENCC>
Take off your hat.
<SYNC Start=536935><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=536937><P Class=ENCC>
- This is bullshit.<br>- What did you just--
<SYNC Start=539638><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=539640><P Class=ENCC>
this is just you trying to talk to me.
<SYNC Start=541706><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=543643><P Class=ENCC>
There are things we need to talk about.
<SYNC Start=545677><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=547780><P Class=ENCC>
There are things that you need to learn.
<SYNC Start=549247><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=549249><P Class=ENCC>
What, are you serious?
<SYNC Start=551149><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=552818><P Class=ENCC>
What is it? Do you-- do you blame me?
<SYNC Start=555287><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=557924><P Class=ENCC>
Huh? Do you actually blame me?
<SYNC Start=560625><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=562061><P Class=ENCC>
Raise your left arm above your head.
<SYNC Start=564563><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=567033><P Class=ENCC>
You can't. Tell me why.
<SYNC Start=569935><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=569937><P Class=ENCC>
No.
<SYNC Start=571670><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=573639><P Class=ENCC>
Your father was dangerous.
<SYNC Start=576107><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=576109><P Class=ENCC>
Rick is dangerous.
<SYNC Start=578076><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=578078><P Class=ENCC>
He doesn't have anything to do with this.
<SYNC Start=579811><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=581347><P Class=ENCC>
What, is he your friend?
<SYNC Start=583281><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=585117><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah, he's my friend.
<SYNC Start=587352><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=599967><P Class=ENCC>
but we don't have to wait<br>to start growing things.
<SYNC Start=604002><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=604004><P Class=ENCC>
There will be some sore<br>backs and tired feet.
<SYNC Start=607105><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=607107><P Class=ENCC>
That's how you know you've<br>put in a hard day's work.
<SYNC Start=609941><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=619218><P Class=ENCC>
They found crates of these at a<br>nursery just a few miles out.
<SYNC Start=623288><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=623290><P Class=ENCC>
Tomatoes, carrots, you name it.
<SYNC Start=626091><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=626093><P Class=ENCC>
We can plant them right here.
<SYNC Start=628727><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=628729><P Class=ENCC>
Just need to finish the expansion
<SYNC Start=632163><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=632165><P Class=ENCC>
and the wall needs to go up.
<SYNC Start=635867><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=635869><P Class=ENCC>
Reg wanted this community to grow.
<SYNC Start=639404><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=639406><P Class=ENCC>
You did, too.
<SYNC Start=642340><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=642342><P Class=ENCC>
Has that changed?
<SYNC Start=644342><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=648881><P Class=ENCC>
Everyone that's here is here because of you.
<SYNC Start=651016><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=654120><P Class=ENCC>
You need to show them you're still here.
<SYNC Start=656721><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=666165><P Class=ENCC>
It hams my biscuits is all.
<SYNC Start=669234><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=669236><P Class=ENCC>
And going by cubic feet,<br>the biggest building in the expansion
<SYNC Start=672203><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=672205><P Class=ENCC>
and we're gonna waste it on a church.
<SYNC Start=674172><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=674174><P Class=ENCC>
Take out the benches, that could be a lab,
<SYNC Start=676207><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=676209><P Class=ENCC>
a machine shop, very least<br>a sweet-ass game room.
<SYNC Start=679077><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=679079><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Walled-in real estate is at a premium here.</i>
<SYNC Start=681379><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=681381><P Class=ENCC>
Thumpers just shouldn't get dibs.
<SYNC Start=683281><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=683283><P Class=ENCC>
Well, maybe we share the church, you know?
<SYNC Start=686284><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=686286><P Class=ENCC>
Do all that stuff on different days.
<SYNC Start=687819><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=687821><P Class=ENCC>
Hams my biscuits?
<SYNC Start=689287><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=689289><P Class=ENCC>
Hams my biscuits. That's all I heard.
<SYNC Start=693091><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=693093><P Class=ENCC>
I mean, I have no idea<br>what you said after that.
<SYNC Start=695427><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=695429><P Class=ENCC>
- Going by cubic feet--<br>- <i>I was kidding.</i>
<SYNC Start=698029><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=700700><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Are you okay, Dana?</i>
<SYNC Start=702434><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=702436><P Class=ENCC>
- It's Denise.<br>- Denise, I'm sorry.
<SYNC Start=705336><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=705338><P Class=ENCC>
I'm okay.
<SYNC Start=707772><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=707774><P Class=ENCC>
I'm the new doctor now.
<SYNC Start=710075><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=710077><P Class=ENCC>
What's the aspirin for?
<SYNC Start=711876><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=711878><P Class=ENCC>
- You're a doctor?<br>- <i>Are you?</i>
<SYNC Start=715013><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=715015><P Class=ENCC>
I'm sorry. I, uh...
<SYNC Start=717916><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=717918><P Class=ENCC>
Heard that story.
<SYNC Start=719818><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=719820><P Class=ENCC>
Fair play.
<SYNC Start=721319><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=721321><P Class=ENCC>
Listen, I'm a little nervous here.
<SYNC Start=723488><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=723490><P Class=ENCC>
I'm a psychiatrist.
<SYNC Start=725757><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=725759><P Class=ENCC>
I went to med school.
<SYNC Start=727392><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=727394><P Class=ENCC>
<i>I was even gonna be a surgeon,</i>
<SYNC Start=728827><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=728829><P Class=ENCC>
but after the panic attacks,
<SYNC Start=730495><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=730497><P Class=ENCC>
I got really interested in psychology.
<SYNC Start=733064><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=733066><P Class=ENCC>
And...
<SYNC Start=736835><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=736837><P Class=ENCC>
I think I'm really trying<br>to lower expectations here.
<SYNC Start=739504><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=739506><P Class=ENCC>
Can you do this?
<SYNC Start=741072><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=741074><P Class=ENCC>
Eugene, shut up. She can do this.
<SYNC Start=744175><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=744177><P Class=ENCC>
I'm all this town's got.
<SYNC Start=745944><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=745946><P Class=ENCC>
Pete didn't want me here.
<SYNC Start=748747><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=748749><P Class=ENCC>
But I'm here now
<SYNC Start=751449><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=751451><P Class=ENCC>
and I only kind of want to throw up.
<SYNC Start=753952><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=754987><P Class=ENCC>
<i>So why the aspirin?</i>
<SYNC Start=756921><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=756923><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, Eugene and I were working on a<br>platform for another guard tower.
<SYNC Start=760258><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=760260><P Class=ENCC>
<i>I got a little dizzy. You know,<br>I still get headaches.</i>
<SYNC Start=763061><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=763063><P Class=ENCC>
Sit down, I'll take a look.
<SYNC Start=764496><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=771304><P Class=ENCC>
You're my first patient.
<SYNC Start=773371><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=773373><P Class=ENCC>
And with that symptom,<br>I'm pretty sure I can't kill you.
<SYNC Start=777442><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=777444><P Class=ENCC>
I mean, it is possible if you miss,<br>like, a hematoma or something.
<SYNC Start=780845><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=804804><P Class=ENCC>
Carl?
<SYNC Start=806938><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=807940><P Class=ENCC>
What?
<SYNC Start=809507><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=810943><P Class=ENCC>
You heard what I told<br>Deanna about your group.
<SYNC Start=814345><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=814347><P Class=ENCC>
What do you want?
<SYNC Start=815914><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=815916><P Class=ENCC>
It was about me,
<SYNC Start=817849><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=817851><P Class=ENCC>
not you or your group.
<SYNC Start=821386><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=821388><P Class=ENCC>
I know that now.
<SYNC Start=823421><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=824957><P Class=ENCC>
I want to help.
<SYNC Start=827392><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=827394><P Class=ENCC>
You tried to teach me back at my church.
<SYNC Start=830995><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=830997><P Class=ENCC>
But I'm ready to learn now.
<SYNC Start=834232><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=835568><P Class=ENCC>
I think you need to tell everybody.
<SYNC Start=838236><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=841874><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah, I think you're right.
<SYNC Start=843975><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=847947><P Class=ENCC>
Come by around 3:00.
<SYNC Start=849981><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=849983><P Class=ENCC>
We'll start with the machete.
<SYNC Start=852050><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=914313><P Class=ENCC>
No! No! No!
<SYNC Start=916581><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=925357><P Class=ENCC>
Richards. What's going on in there?
<SYNC Start=928426><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=932599><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, no.
<SYNC Start=934132><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=934134><P Class=ENCC>
No.
<SYNC Start=935633><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=945945><P Class=ENCC>
Come on!
<SYNC Start=947545><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=954453><P Class=ENCC>
<i>I saw from upstairs.</i>
<SYNC Start=955954><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=955956><P Class=ENCC>
They're coming in from all over.
<SYNC Start=957355><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=957357><P Class=ENCC>
You have to stay here and keep Judith safe.
<SYNC Start=959691><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=964596><P Class=ENCC>
- Please don't go.<br>- I have to go find Ron.
<SYNC Start=966965><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=966967><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, please. Please don't go.
<SYNC Start=968599><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=968601><P Class=ENCC>
- I'm gonna be right back, okay? - Mom, no.
<SYNC Start=971069><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=971071><P Class=ENCC>
No, you go put yourself in the closet
<SYNC Start=972971><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=972973><P Class=ENCC>
and you close the latch<br>just like I showed you.
<SYNC Start=975239><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=978711><P Class=ENCC>
Shh. Shh. Shh.
<SYNC Start=981546><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1028160><P Class=ENCC>
Hi.
<SYNC Start=1029594><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1029596><P Class=ENCC>
Why didn't you just knock?
<SYNC Start=1031662><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1031664><P Class=ENCC>
I have these. Didn't want them to have them.
<SYNC Start=1034465><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1040039><P Class=ENCC>
And I wanted to say good-bye.
<SYNC Start=1041773><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1041775><P Class=ENCC>
Okay, watch the back door.<br>Tell me if you see them coming.
<SYNC Start=1044242><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1044244><P Class=ENCC>
- I'm not staying.<br>- You're not going anywhere.
<SYNC Start=1046544><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1046546><P Class=ENCC>
Sit down. You're helping me protect Judith.
<SYNC Start=1049714><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1049716><P Class=ENCC>
They're not getting inside this house.
<SYNC Start=1051816><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1059558><P Class=ENCC>
We're not gonna let them.
<SYNC Start=1061559><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1064830><P Class=ENCC>
Did you see them?
<SYNC Start=1066697><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1067833><P Class=ENCC>
They're just people.
<SYNC Start=1070168><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1071737><P Class=ENCC>
This place is too big to protect.
<SYNC Start=1075239><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1075241><P Class=ENCC>
There are too many blind spots.
<SYNC Start=1078176><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1078178><P Class=ENCC>
That's how we were able to--
<SYNC Start=1080178><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1080180><P Class=ENCC>
they got in the walls,<br>but they're gonna die.
<SYNC Start=1083414><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1085317><P Class=ENCC>
All of them.
<SYNC Start=1086317><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1090689><P Class=ENCC>
Don't tell me good-bye.
<SYNC Start=1093157><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1101133><P Class=ENCC>
Okay.
<SYNC Start=1103201><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1106338><P Class=ENCC>
I won't.
<SYNC Start=1108206><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1152384><P Class=ENCC>
<i>No, please. Please don't.</i>
<SYNC Start=1154352><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1154354><P Class=ENCC>
<i>No, please. Please...</i>
<SYNC Start=1156487><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1156489><P Class=ENCC>
Go away!
<SYNC Start=1157889><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1162194><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, god.
<SYNC Start=1165296><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1166365><P Class=ENCC>
Shh.
<SYNC Start=1168466><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1173907><P Class=ENCC>
Shh. Shh.
<SYNC Start=1178209><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1211945><P Class=ENCC>
Shit.
<SYNC Start=1213911><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1213913><P Class=ENCC>
Come on. Come on.
<SYNC Start=1216781><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1268000><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Holly!</i>
<SYNC Start=1270301><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1270303><P Class=ENCC>
We need the operating table prepped.
<SYNC Start=1271936><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1271938><P Class=ENCC>
She's lost a lot of blood.<br>Come on, come on, come on.
<SYNC Start=1274772><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1274774><P Class=ENCC>
- How many people are out there?<br>- I don't know, there's a lot.
<SYNC Start=1277508><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1277510><P Class=ENCC>
Rosita, you know how to stick an iv?
<SYNC Start=1279443><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1279445><P Class=ENCC>
I'm on it. Here, hand me tape.
<SYNC Start=1281912><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1281914><P Class=ENCC>
- Got it. - What about the air horn?<br>What's happening?
<SYNC Start=1283681><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1283683><P Class=ENCC>
I don't know. I need to help.
<SYNC Start=1286017><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1286019><P Class=ENCC>
- I need to try.<br>- I know.
<SYNC Start=1288352><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1288354><P Class=ENCC>
Denise, I'm gonna have to go, too.
<SYNC Start=1290955><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1292992><P Class=ENCC>
You got dizzy swinging a hammer.
<SYNC Start=1295593><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1295595><P Class=ENCC>
Somebody's got to guard this place.
<SYNC Start=1296827><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1296829><P Class=ENCC>
- You can handle it.<br>- I can't!
<SYNC Start=1298896><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1298898><P Class=ENCC>
I also believe my services would<br>be best rendered right very here.
<SYNC Start=1301065><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1301067><P Class=ENCC>
- What? - I also believe my services--
<SYNC Start=1303000><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1303002><P Class=ENCC>
shut up! You're safe here. Come on.
<SYNC Start=1304869><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1339938><P Class=ENCC>
What happened?
<SYNC Start=1341539><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1341541><P Class=ENCC>
Someone, a group, they got inside the walls.
<SYNC Start=1344842><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1344844><P Class=ENCC>
They're killing people.
<SYNC Start=1346577><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1346579><P Class=ENCC>
<i>We need to get in there.</i>
<SYNC Start=1348746><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1351583><P Class=ENCC>
<i>You coming?</i>
<SYNC Start=1353050><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1356955><P Class=ENCC>
Hide.
<SYNC Start=1358622><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1380579><P Class=ENCC>
Quick...
<SYNC Start=1382012><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1383915><P Class=ENCC>
Or slow?
<SYNC Start=1385683><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1387486><P Class=ENCC>
Leave.
<SYNC Start=1389787><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1389789><P Class=ENCC>
Please.
<SYNC Start=1391455><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1393625><P Class=ENCC>
Gonna be slow.
<SYNC Start=1395559><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1403969><P Class=ENCC>
I could have stopped him.
<SYNC Start=1405436><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1405438><P Class=ENCC>
- The others back?<br>- No.
<SYNC Start=1407538><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1407540><P Class=ENCC>
- It's happening out there.<br>- <i>They're doing it now?</i>
<SYNC Start=1409640><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1409642><P Class=ENCC>
We had to.
<SYNC Start=1411642><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1411644><P Class=ENCC>
- These people don't have guns.<br><i>- I could have stopped him.</i>
<SYNC Start=1414645><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1414647><P Class=ENCC>
If they had guns, they'd be<br>using them. - Did you hear me?
<SYNC Start=1417481><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1417483><P Class=ENCC>
<i>We have to get to the armory before they do.</i>
<SYNC Start=1419650><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1419652><P Class=ENCC>
<i>If we keep moving, this might work.</i>
<SYNC Start=1422119><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1422121><P Class=ENCC>
You don't have to kill people.
<SYNC Start=1423687><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1423689><P Class=ENCC>
- Of course we do.<br>- <i>Carol!</i>
<SYNC Start=1426991><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1426993><P Class=ENCC>
You don't like it.
<SYNC Start=1429493><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1432664><P Class=ENCC>
I'm gonna get to the armory<br>and I need your help.
<SYNC Start=1435599><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1440939><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Mom!</i>
<SYNC Start=1442673><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1442675><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, god. Spencer.
<SYNC Start=1444942><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1444944><P Class=ENCC>
Thank god.
<SYNC Start=1446677><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1446679><P Class=ENCC>
Thank god.
<SYNC Start=1448212><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1448214><P Class=ENCC>
We need to get inside.
<SYNC Start=1450548><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1450550><P Class=ENCC>
I can't go in there. I don't have a gun.
<SYNC Start=1452783><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1452785><P Class=ENCC>
I don't know how to fight.
<SYNC Start=1454852><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1454854><P Class=ENCC>
If I go inside, I'll just be another<br>person who's got to be saved.
<SYNC Start=1458656><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1458658><P Class=ENCC>
Best thing that I can<br>do for everyone in there
<SYNC Start=1462827><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1462829><P Class=ENCC>
is to stay out here.
<SYNC Start=1465162><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1466731><P Class=ENCC>
- Keep her safe.<br>- I will.
<SYNC Start=1468666><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1499264><P Class=ENCC>
<i>What's happening with her? </i></i>
<SYNC Start=1501499><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1501501><P Class=ENCC>
She's bleeding internally.
<SYNC Start=1503801><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1503803><P Class=ENCC>
Probably severed her femoral artery.
<SYNC Start=1507037><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1507039><P Class=ENCC>
She's dying.
<SYNC Start=1509039><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1509041><P Class=ENCC>
Okay, so the artery's severed.<br>Can it be fixed?
<SYNC Start=1511742><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1511744><P Class=ENCC>
Maybe by a surgeon.
<SYNC Start=1513811><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1513813><P Class=ENCC>
You were gonna be a surgeon.
<SYNC Start=1515279><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1515281><P Class=ENCC>
But I'm not.
<SYNC Start=1516814><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1516816><P Class=ENCC>
She was protecting this place.
<SYNC Start=1518949><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1518951><P Class=ENCC>
She was guarding us. That's why<br>we're here, for each other.
<SYNC Start=1521952><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1523788><P Class=ENCC>
You're afraid?
<SYNC Start=1526090><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1526092><P Class=ENCC>
I don't care. Help her.
<SYNC Start=1528626><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1529761><P Class=ENCC>
Try! Help her!
<SYNC Start=1533030><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1535301><P Class=ENCC>
You don't want to be a coward.
<SYNC Start=1537735><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1537737><P Class=ENCC>
I know.
<SYNC Start=1539904><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1548046><P Class=ENCC>
I need an abdominal binder.<br>We're gonna pull the knife.
<SYNC Start=1550214><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1550216><P Class=ENCC>
Okay. Okay.
<SYNC Start=1552049><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1557322><P Class=ENCC>
Okay. Okay. Come on.
<SYNC Start=1560824><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1570770><P Class=ENCC>
Shit!
<SYNC Start=1573270><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1577842><P Class=ENCC>
Please, man. Please don't kill me, man.
<SYNC Start=1580778><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1580780><P Class=ENCC>
Please. Help me, please. My leg.
<SYNC Start=1583647><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1595293><P Class=ENCC>
Come inside.
<SYNC Start=1597828><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1597830><P Class=ENCC>
I can keep you safe.
<SYNC Start=1599330><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1605837><P Class=ENCC>
No.
<SYNC Start=1607838><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1607840><P Class=ENCC>
Ron.
<SYNC Start=1609974><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1612911><P Class=ENCC>
Carl, come on!
<SYNC Start=1615379><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1625890><P Class=ENCC>
<i>on: Mom.</i>
<SYNC Start=1627791><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1627793><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Mom, you in? </i></i>
<SYNC Start=1630728><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1637869><P Class=ENCC>
Lock it. Be brave.
<SYNC Start=1640137><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1657956><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Stay outside, Ron!</i>
<SYNC Start=1661058><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1669901><P Class=ENCC>
No!
<SYNC Start=1671335><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1726324><P Class=ENCC>
Good catch, aphid.
<SYNC Start=1728292><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1731262><P Class=ENCC>
Come on. Leave him.
<SYNC Start=1733497><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1733499><P Class=ENCC>
No.
<SYNC Start=1735299><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1740839><P Class=ENCC>
Hey, aphid, where'd you get the gun?
<SYNC Start=1742840><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1754352><P Class=ENCC>
You're dead.
<SYNC Start=1756186><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1803468><P Class=ENCC>
Please don't kill me.
<SYNC Start=1805102><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1807505><P Class=ENCC>
It's okay. Anybody else down here?
<SYNC Start=1810974><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1812510><P Class=ENCC>
- Olivia!<br>- No.
<SYNC Start=1814478><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1814480><P Class=ENCC>
No, I'm the only one.
<SYNC Start=1816513><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1822587><P Class=ENCC>
Come here.
<SYNC Start=1824521><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1824523><P Class=ENCC>
Now.
<SYNC Start=1826323><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1828560><P Class=ENCC>
You barricade that door<br>behind me once I leave.
<SYNC Start=1831028><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1831030><P Class=ENCC>
Do you know how to shoot a gun?
<SYNC Start=1833330><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1833332><P Class=ENCC>
Stand here.
<SYNC Start=1835132><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1835134><P Class=ENCC>
Finger here. Aim there.
<SYNC Start=1837201><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1837203><P Class=ENCC>
One of them comes through that door,
<SYNC Start=1839303><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1839305><P Class=ENCC>
you squeeze and you don't stop<br>till they're on the ground.
<SYNC Start=1841505><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1852884><P Class=ENCC>
How did you learn how to do that?
<SYNC Start=1854484><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1856187><P Class=ENCC>
From a cheese maker.
<SYNC Start=1858488><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1864863><P Class=ENCC>
We're freeing you.
<SYNC Start=1866897><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1866899><P Class=ENCC>
You're trapped.
<SYNC Start=1869099><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1869101><P Class=ENCC>
You need to know,<br>people don't belong here anymore.
<SYNC Start=1872569><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1884115><P Class=ENCC>
- Carol?<br>- Maggie!
<SYNC Start=1886250><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1891356><P Class=ENCC>
- Here.<br>- I--
<SYNC Start=1894024><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1894026><P Class=ENCC>
I'm not very good with guns. I--
<SYNC Start=1896493><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1896495><P Class=ENCC>
me neither.
<SYNC Start=1898362><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1956354><P Class=ENCC>
You.
<SYNC Start=1958355><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1958357><P Class=ENCC>
You live here?
<SYNC Start=1960123><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1969300><P Class=ENCC>
Leave.
<SYNC Start=1971702><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1973304><P Class=ENCC>
My people have guns.
<SYNC Start=1976139><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1979177><P Class=ENCC>
Yours don't.
<SYNC Start=1982212><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1982214><P Class=ENCC>
They may be aiming rifles at you right now.
<SYNC Start=1985682><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1986751><P Class=ENCC>
Eyes at the scopes.
<SYNC Start=1988719><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1988721><P Class=ENCC>
Fingers on the trigger.
<SYNC Start=1991088><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1992423><P Class=ENCC>
Boom.
<SYNC Start=1994691><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1994693><P Class=ENCC>
It's gonna happen any second now
<SYNC Start=1996693><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1996695><P Class=ENCC>
unless you get the hell out of<br>here and you don't ever come back.
<SYNC Start=1999429><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2001499><P Class=ENCC>
You keep choosing this life,
<SYNC Start=2004634><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2004636><P Class=ENCC>
you will die.
<SYNC Start=2006636><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2008539><P Class=ENCC>
We didn't choose.
<SYNC Start=2011174><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2188954><P Class=ENCC>
Come on, Holly.
<SYNC Start=2190754><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2221919><P Class=ENCC>
Denise, you tried.
<SYNC Start=2223853><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2223855><P Class=ENCC>
You are a doctor.
<SYNC Start=2225555><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2225557><P Class=ENCC>
Just go see if it's over out there
<SYNC Start=2228825><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2228827><P Class=ENCC>
and if...
<SYNC Start=2230660><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2232697><P Class=ENCC>
Please go, all of you.
<SYNC Start=2234864><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2234866><P Class=ENCC>
- Okay, but I just--<br>- good. Go.
<SYNC Start=2237934><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2248546><P Class=ENCC>
All I was gonna say is...
<SYNC Start=2250447><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2251782><P Class=ENCC>
Ahem, make sure you get her brain.
<SYNC Start=2254951><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2266898><P Class=ENCC>
What happened today,
<SYNC Start=2269266><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2269268><P Class=ENCC>
that's what it's like out there?
<SYNC Start=2270900><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2270902><P Class=ENCC>
Pretty much.
<SYNC Start=2272669><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2272671><P Class=ENCC>
How do you--
<SYNC Start=2274771><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2274773><P Class=ENCC>
how do you just live<br>knowing that's the world?
<SYNC Start=2278408><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2282813><P Class=ENCC>
This group,
<SYNC Start=2285682><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2285684><P Class=ENCC>
Abraham, and this place.
<SYNC Start=2287817><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2290388><P Class=ENCC>
Make sure you got something worth dying for.
<SYNC Start=2292455><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2316681><P Class=ENCC>
We're still here.
<SYNC Start=2318515><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2319950><P Class=ENCC>
Not all of us.
<SYNC Start=2321885><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2338036><P Class=ENCC>
Enid?
<SYNC Start=2340003><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2341706><P Class=ENCC>
Enid?
<SYNC Start=2343573><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2471969><P Class=ENCC>
You can't, can you?
<SYNC Start=2474170><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2478242><P Class=ENCC>
You should've.
<SYNC Start=2480009><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2492756><P Class=ENCC>
I'm sorry.
<SYNC Start=2494791><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp

</BODY>
</SAMI>
