<SAMI>
<HEAD>
<HEAD>
<TITLE></TITLE>
<STYLE TYPE="text/css">
<!--
P { margin-left:8pt; margin-right:8pt; margin-bottom:2pt; margin-top:2pt;
    text-align:center;
    font-size:20pt; font-family:arial, sans-serif; font-weight:normal; color:white; }
.ENCC { Name:English; lang:en-US; SAMIType:CC;}
#STDPrn { Name:Standard Print;}
#LargePrn { Name:Large Print; font-size:25pt;}
#SmallPrn { Name:Small Print; font-size:15pt;}
-->
</STYLE>
</HEAD>
<BODY>
<SYNC Start=353><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Previously on AMC's<br>The Walking Dead...</i>
<SYNC Start=3739><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3958><P Class=ENCC>
- We drew them out.<br>- We should go out after them.
<SYNC Start=5733><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5844><P Class=ENCC>
We should finish it.
<SYNC Start=7281><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=7436><P Class=ENCC>
How you live, how you die...
<SYNC Start=9686><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=9795><P Class=ENCC>
it isn't up to me.
<SYNC Start=11079><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=11241><P Class=ENCC>
We vote.
<SYNC Start=12458><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=14114><P Class=ENCC>
He gunned that kid down.
<SYNC Start=15764><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=15895><P Class=ENCC>
I did what I had to do.
<SYNC Start=17648><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=18348><P Class=ENCC>
No, we're all infected.
<SYNC Start=19550><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=19694><P Class=ENCC>
♪<br>you come back as one of these things.
<SYNC Start=22123><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=22234><P Class=ENCC>
Where is the Governor!?
<SYNC Start=23142><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=23231><P Class=ENCC>
He fired on everyone.<br>Killed them all.
<SYNC Start=25386><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=26225><P Class=ENCC>
♪ us.
<SYNC Start=27951><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=31997><P Class=ENCC>
( birds chirping, cawing )
<SYNC Start=33998><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=48915><P Class=ENCC>
( sighs )
<SYNC Start=51016><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=56723><P Class=ENCC>
<i>♪ As I travel ♪</i>
<SYNC Start=61059><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=61060><P Class=ENCC>
♪ Down life's pathways ♪
<SYNC Start=65197><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=65198><P Class=ENCC>
<i>♪ Knowing not what ♪</i>
<SYNC Start=67833><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=67834><P Class=ENCC>
<i>♪ The years may hold ♪</i>
<SYNC Start=72170><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=73373><P Class=ENCC>
<i>♪ As I ponder... ♪</i>
<SYNC Start=77259><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=77260><P Class=ENCC>
- ( clanking )<br>- <i>♪ Hopes grow fonder ♪</i>
<SYNC Start=81546><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=81547><P Class=ENCC>
<i>♪ Precious sacred ♪</i>
<SYNC Start=84583><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=84584><P Class=ENCC>
<i>♪ Scenes unfold ♪</i>
<SYNC Start=87185><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=89572><P Class=ENCC>
- <i>♪ Precious... ♪</i><br><i>- ( walkers growling )</i>
<SYNC Start=92224><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=94560><P Class=ENCC>
<i>( fence rattling )</i>
<SYNC Start=97162><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=97163><P Class=ENCC>
( snarling )
<SYNC Start=99731><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=118017><P Class=ENCC>
<i>♪ Precious father ♪</i>
<SYNC Start=121520><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=121521><P Class=ENCC>
<i>♪ Loving mother ♪</i>
<SYNC Start=125891><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=125892><P Class=ENCC>
<i>♪ Fly across ♪</i>
<SYNC Start=128810><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=128811><P Class=ENCC>
♪ The lonely years... ♪
<SYNC Start=132447><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=132448><P Class=ENCC>
( theme music playing )
<SYNC Start=134449><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=163240><P Class=ENCC>
Sync and corrections by n17t01<br>www.addic7ed.com
<SYNC Start=167746><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=176955><P Class=ENCC>
You didn't wake me up.
<SYNC Start=178655><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=178656><P Class=ENCC>
'Cause I knew you were up all night<br>reading comics with a flashlight.
<SYNC Start=181575><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=185980><P Class=ENCC>
Carl:<br><i>What's up with Violet?</i>
<SYNC Start=188315><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=188316><P Class=ENCC>
Carl, I told you<br>not to name them.
<SYNC Start=190584><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=190585><P Class=ENCC>
They're not piglets anymore.<br>They're food.
<SYNC Start=193286><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=193287><P Class=ENCC>
I just thought,<br>you know, until...
<SYNC Start=196006><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=197509><P Class=ENCC>
Okay.
<SYNC Start=199343><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=202597><P Class=ENCC>
I don't know<br>what's going on with her.
<SYNC Start=204832><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=204833><P Class=ENCC>
Could be sick,<br>could be nothing.
<SYNC Start=207668><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=207669><P Class=ENCC>
( clicking tongue )
<SYNC Start=209570><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=209571><P Class=ENCC>
Feel better, Violet.
<SYNC Start=211488><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=213191><P Class=ENCC>
Come on, let's get to it.
<SYNC Start=215409><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=216861><P Class=ENCC>
- Morning, Daryl.<br>- What's up, Dr. S?
<SYNC Start=219163><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=219164><P Class=ENCC>
- Man: Morning, Daryl.<br>- Man #2: <i>Morning, Daryl.</i>
<SYNC Start=220747><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=220748><P Class=ENCC>
Woman:<br><i>Hey, Daryl!</i>
<SYNC Start=222332><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=222333><P Class=ENCC>
Smells good.
<SYNC Start=224651><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=224652><P Class=ENCC>
Just so you know,<br>I liked you first.
<SYNC Start=227254><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=227255><P Class=ENCC>
Stop.
<SYNC Start=228872><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=230825><P Class=ENCC>
You know, Rick brought in<br>a lot of them, too.
<SYNC Start=233326><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=233327><P Class=ENCC>
Not recently.
<SYNC Start=236163><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=236164><P Class=ENCC>
Give the stranger sanctuary,
<SYNC Start=238398><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=238399><P Class=ENCC>
keeping people fed,
<SYNC Start=239967><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=239968><P Class=ENCC>
you're gonna have to learn<br>to live with the love.
<SYNC Start=241685><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=241686><P Class=ENCC>
- Right.<br>- I need you to see something.
<SYNC Start=244504><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=244505><P Class=ENCC>
Patrick, you want to take over?
<SYNC Start=246023><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=246024><P Class=ENCC>
Yes, ma'am.
<SYNC Start=247691><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=250195><P Class=ENCC>
Mr. Dixon,
<SYNC Start=252512><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=252513><P Class=ENCC>
I just wanted to thank you for<br>bringing that deer back yesterday.
<SYNC Start=255699><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=255700><P Class=ENCC>
It was a real treat, sir.
<SYNC Start=257951><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=257952><P Class=ENCC>
And I'd be honored<br>to shake your hand.
<SYNC Start=260187><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=273218><P Class=ENCC>
( growling )
<SYNC Start=275702><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=310538><P Class=ENCC>
About today, I don't know<br>if we're gonna be able
<SYNC Start=313740><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=313741><P Class=ENCC>
to spare a lot of people<br>for the run.
<SYNC Start=316210><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=316211><P Class=ENCC>
That place is good to go.<br>We're gonna move on it.
<SYNC Start=318428><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=318429><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah.
<SYNC Start=320714><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=320715><P Class=ENCC>
The thing is, we had a pretty<br>big buildup overnight.
<SYNC Start=324051><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=324052><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Dozens more</i><br><i>towards tower three.</i>
<SYNC Start=326303><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=327956><P Class=ENCC>
<i>It's getting as bad</i><br><i>as last month.</i>
<SYNC Start=329823><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=329824><P Class=ENCC>
<i>They don't spread out anymore.</i>
<SYNC Start=331458><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=331459><P Class=ENCC>
With more of us sitting here,<br>we're drawing more of them out.
<SYNC Start=334094><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=334095><P Class=ENCC>
You get enough of those damn<br>fence-clingers, they start to herd up.
<SYNC Start=337030><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=337031><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Pushing against</i><br><i>the fences again.</i>
<SYNC Start=339099><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=339100><P Class=ENCC>
It's manageable, but unless we<br>get ahead of it, not for long.
<SYNC Start=342336><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=342337><P Class=ENCC>
Sorry, Pookie.
<SYNC Start=344271><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=345306><P Class=ENCC>
( scoffs )
<SYNC Start=347908><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=347909><P Class=ENCC>
( snarling )
<SYNC Start=349626><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=358469><P Class=ENCC>
You like that?
<SYNC Start=359686><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=377572><P Class=ENCC>
( sighs )
<SYNC Start=379973><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=388816><P Class=ENCC>
I don't think<br>you should go today.
<SYNC Start=391168><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=393621><P Class=ENCC>
Really?
<SYNC Start=395622><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=395623><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah.
<SYNC Start=397157><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=401462><P Class=ENCC>
We have the suits.
<SYNC Start=403163><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=403164><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah, but you don't have to go.
<SYNC Start=405349><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=405350><P Class=ENCC>
You shouldn't.
<SYNC Start=407167><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=410221><P Class=ENCC>
You know everything's<br>gonna work out, right?
<SYNC Start=412773><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=414976><P Class=ENCC>
Right?
<SYNC Start=416509><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=417862><P Class=ENCC>
Right.
<SYNC Start=419512><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=420681><P Class=ENCC>
Right.
<SYNC Start=422182><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=423368><P Class=ENCC>
But you're staying, okay?
<SYNC Start=425369><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=427705><P Class=ENCC>
Fine.
<SYNC Start=429522><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=431709><P Class=ENCC>
Hey, beautiful.
<SYNC Start=433994><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=433995><P Class=ENCC>
Hey yourself.
<SYNC Start=435829><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=435830><P Class=ENCC>
- You need an apron.<br>- Yeah.
<SYNC Start=438665><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=438666><P Class=ENCC>
Listen, can we talk?
<SYNC Start=440884><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=446140><P Class=ENCC>
I was thinking of going<br>on the run today.
<SYNC Start=448308><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=448309><P Class=ENCC>
Okay.
<SYNC Start=449943><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=449944><P Class=ENCC>
I don't like killing<br>them on the fence.
<SYNC Start=452946><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=452947><P Class=ENCC>
I hate it.
<SYNC Start=454881><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=454882><P Class=ENCC>
I mean, when they're<br>coming at you out there,
<SYNC Start=457050><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=457051><P Class=ENCC>
it's different.
<SYNC Start=458685><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=458686><P Class=ENCC>
You don't even think about it.
<SYNC Start=460520><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=460521><P Class=ENCC>
When they're stacked up<br>against the chain-link,
<SYNC Start=463223><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=463224><P Class=ENCC>
you're just face-to-face.
<SYNC Start=466226><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=466227><P Class=ENCC>
I...
<SYNC Start=468095><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=470398><P Class=ENCC>
I just wanted to do something<br>different to help out.
<SYNC Start=473033><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=474836><P Class=ENCC>
You always volunteered to do it.
<SYNC Start=477938><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=477939><P Class=ENCC>
That's because you<br>were always doing it.
<SYNC Start=480090><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=480091><P Class=ENCC>
( laughs )
<SYNC Start=482409><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=482410><P Class=ENCC>
Just thought I could<br>get to know you.
<SYNC Start=485045><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=490301><P Class=ENCC>
You did.
<SYNC Start=492219><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=494322><P Class=ENCC>
You be careful out there.
<SYNC Start=496940><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=507402><P Class=ENCC>
Hey.
<SYNC Start=509569><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=509570><P Class=ENCC>
I was just gonna come find you.
<SYNC Start=511538><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=513941><P Class=ENCC>
- Hi.<br>- What's up?
<SYNC Start=516660><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=516661><P Class=ENCC>
Well, the council pulled back<br>everyone on the coal crew
<SYNC Start=519963><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=519964><P Class=ENCC>
from going on the run.
<SYNC Start=521915><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=521916><P Class=ENCC>
They're shorthanded right now.
<SYNC Start=523717><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=523718><P Class=ENCC>
I figured I'd step up<br>to help, go with 'em.
<SYNC Start=525836><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=527788><P Class=ENCC>
Just, you know, wanted to make<br>sure that I saw you before.
<SYNC Start=530190><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=531225><P Class=ENCC>
Okay.
<SYNC Start=533009><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=533010><P Class=ENCC>
I just--<br>'cause, you know,
<SYNC Start=534561><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=534562><P Class=ENCC>
it's dangerous going out there.
<SYNC Start=536930><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=536931><P Class=ENCC>
I know.<br>( kisses )
<SYNC Start=539182><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=542019><P Class=ENCC>
Okay, are you<br>gonna say good-bye?
<SYNC Start=543904><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=543905><P Class=ENCC>
Nope.
<SYNC Start=545489><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=545490><P Class=ENCC>
It's like a damn romance novel.
<SYNC Start=547657><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=555500><P Class=ENCC>
Hey.
<SYNC Start=558368><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=558369><P Class=ENCC>
I'd like to start pulling<br>my weight around here.
<SYNC Start=560370><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=560371><P Class=ENCC>
Bob, it's only been a week.
<SYNC Start=561788><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=561789><P Class=ENCC>
That's a week worth of meals,
<SYNC Start=563623><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=563624><P Class=ENCC>
a roof over my head.
<SYNC Start=565759><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=565760><P Class=ENCC>
Let me earn my keep.
<SYNC Start=567494><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=570848><P Class=ENCC>
- You were out on your own<br>when Daryl found you. - That's right.
<SYNC Start=573767><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=573768><P Class=ENCC>
<i>I just want to make sure you<br>know how to play on a team.</i>
<SYNC Start=576336><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=576337><P Class=ENCC>
We ain't gonna do it<br>unless it's easy.
<SYNC Start=578054><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=578055><P Class=ENCC>
You know he was<br>a medic in the Army.
<SYNC Start=579806><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=584312><P Class=ENCC>
You a hell of a tough sell.<br>You know that?
<SYNC Start=586846><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=588733><P Class=ENCC>
Okay.
<SYNC Start=590350><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=590351><P Class=ENCC>
( engines start )
<SYNC Start=592285><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=593654><P Class=ENCC>
These leaves are gonna<br>be in the shade,
<SYNC Start=596389><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=596390><P Class=ENCC>
so we won't get<br>any good fruit from it.
<SYNC Start=599326><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=599327><P Class=ENCC>
So we just pinch it off here.
<SYNC Start=602362><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=603831><P Class=ENCC>
Things break,<br>but they can still grow.
<SYNC Start=607367><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=607368><P Class=ENCC>
These little bristles,<br>they'll take root
<SYNC Start=610420><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=610421><P Class=ENCC>
and we'll have<br>a whole new plant.
<SYNC Start=612589><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=612590><P Class=ENCC>
<i>( whistles )</i>
<SYNC Start=614874><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=616177><P Class=ENCC>
Rick:<br><i>Let's go.</i>
<SYNC Start=617260><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=617261><P Class=ENCC>
( growling )
<SYNC Start=620380><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=628739><P Class=ENCC>
( grunts )
<SYNC Start=630774><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=651078><P Class=ENCC>
We're glad to see you.
<SYNC Start=652596><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=652597><P Class=ENCC>
Glad to see you, too.
<SYNC Start=654914><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=654915><P Class=ENCC>
Somebody hit the jackpot.
<SYNC Start=656749><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=656750><P Class=ENCC>
No way.
<SYNC Start=658635><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=658636><P Class=ENCC>
Awesome!<br>Thank you.
<SYNC Start=661271><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=661272><P Class=ENCC>
I get to read 'em<br>when you're done.
<SYNC Start=662639><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=662640><P Class=ENCC>
And I found this.
<SYNC Start=665191><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=668262><P Class=ENCC>
Your face is losing the war.
<SYNC Start=670931><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=670932><P Class=ENCC>
( chuckles )
<SYNC Start=672432><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=672433><P Class=ENCC>
You gonna stay a little while?
<SYNC Start=675001><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=675002><P Class=ENCC>
Just a little while.
<SYNC Start=677070><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=677071><P Class=ENCC>
<i>( motorcycle revving )</i>
<SYNC Start=678638><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=685830><P Class=ENCC>
Well, look who's back.
<SYNC Start=687964><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=687965><P Class=ENCC>
Didn't find him.
<SYNC Start=690483><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=691886><P Class=ENCC>
Glad to see you in one piece.
<SYNC Start=694621><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=694622><P Class=ENCC>
I'm thinking of looking<br>over near Macon.
<SYNC Start=696590><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=698342><P Class=ENCC>
It's worth a shot.
<SYNC Start=700093><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=700094><P Class=ENCC>
Daryl:<br>70 miles of walkers.
<SYNC Start=702162><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=702163><P Class=ENCC>
You might run into<br>a few unneighborly types.
<SYNC Start=704964><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=704965><P Class=ENCC>
Is it?
<SYNC Start=706650><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=710304><P Class=ENCC>
I'm gonna go check out<br>the Big Spot.
<SYNC Start=711972><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=711973><P Class=ENCC>
The one I was talking<br>about, just seeing.
<SYNC Start=714708><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=714709><P Class=ENCC>
Rick: Yeah, I got to go<br>out and check the snares.
<SYNC Start=717377><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=717378><P Class=ENCC>
I don't want to lose whatever<br>we catch to the walkers.
<SYNC Start=719946><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=719947><P Class=ENCC>
I'll go.
<SYNC Start=721314><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=721315><P Class=ENCC>
You just got here.
<SYNC Start=723016><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=723017><P Class=ENCC>
And I'll be back.
<SYNC Start=725685><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=727888><P Class=ENCC>
( revs motor )
<SYNC Start=730340><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=730341><P Class=ENCC>
( engine starts )
<SYNC Start=732626><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=736213><P Class=ENCC>
( growling )
<SYNC Start=738298><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=742053><P Class=ENCC>
- Going to check the snares?<br>- I am.
<SYNC Start=744220><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=744221><P Class=ENCC>
You're not.<br>Do your chores.
<SYNC Start=746906><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=746907><P Class=ENCC>
Read comics.<br>Maybe some books, too.
<SYNC Start=749342><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=749343><P Class=ENCC>
Hang out with Patrick.
<SYNC Start=751778><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=751779><P Class=ENCC>
Maybe go to story time.
<SYNC Start=753813><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=753814><P Class=ENCC>
Dad, that's for kids.
<SYNC Start=755949><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=755950><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah.
<SYNC Start=757684><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=759253><P Class=ENCC>
Now brush her down.
<SYNC Start=761187><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=768963><P Class=ENCC>
Nothing wrong with<br>staying close, Rick.
<SYNC Start=772432><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=772433><P Class=ENCC>
Everyone understands.
<SYNC Start=774901><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=774902><P Class=ENCC>
You're growing us enough food
<SYNC Start=776603><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=776604><P Class=ENCC>
so we won't need<br>to do runs soon.
<SYNC Start=778872><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=778873><P Class=ENCC>
But we do have to find you<br>a good pair of overalls.
<SYNC Start=782175><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=782176><P Class=ENCC>
You need to look the part.
<SYNC Start=784561><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=784562><P Class=ENCC>
A little piece of wheat out<br>of the corner of your mouth.
<SYNC Start=786896><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=786897><P Class=ENCC>
Maybe a bigger ass.
<SYNC Start=788381><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=788382><P Class=ENCC>
( laughs )<br>Yeah.
<SYNC Start=791234><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=791235><P Class=ENCC>
Listen, the rest<br>of the council--
<SYNC Start=794888><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=794889><P Class=ENCC>
Daryl, Glenn, Carol, Sasha,
<SYNC Start=797724><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=797725><P Class=ENCC>
all of them--
<SYNC Start=800994><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=800995><P Class=ENCC>
they wanted me to talk to you.
<SYNC Start=803296><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=803297><P Class=ENCC>
When you go out there,
<SYNC Start=806066><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=806067><P Class=ENCC>
you got to take your gun.
<SYNC Start=808268><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=808269><P Class=ENCC>
- ( horse snorts )<br>- Easy now.
<SYNC Start=811004><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=811005><P Class=ENCC>
It's just outside the fence.
<SYNC Start=813373><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=813374><P Class=ENCC>
I have my knife.
<SYNC Start=815508><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=815509><P Class=ENCC>
I get in trouble, six bullets<br>isn't gonna make the difference.
<SYNC Start=818211><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=818212><P Class=ENCC>
Rick, we want you to be safe.
<SYNC Start=821915><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=823217><P Class=ENCC>
Bring your gun.
<SYNC Start=825585><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=832426><P Class=ENCC>
( flies buzzing )
<SYNC Start=834928><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=847708><P Class=ENCC>
( grunting )
<SYNC Start=850710><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=858652><P Class=ENCC>
<i>( rustling )</i>
<SYNC Start=859819><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=868729><P Class=ENCC>
Wait.
<SYNC Start=870730><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=872466><P Class=ENCC>
Please.
<SYNC Start=874768><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=880307><P Class=ENCC>
Please?
<SYNC Start=882475><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=887615><P Class=ENCC>
Please help me.
<SYNC Start=889749><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=892638><P Class=ENCC>
I know you don't know me.
<SYNC Start=894906><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=894907><P Class=ENCC>
Okay, I know that.
<SYNC Start=897875><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=897876><P Class=ENCC>
But can you please help me<br>get this to my husband?
<SYNC Start=901579><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=903248><P Class=ENCC>
We haven't eaten in days.
<SYNC Start=905950><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=928440><P Class=ENCC>
Here.<br>Go ahead.
<SYNC Start=931075><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=938450><P Class=ENCC>
Thank you.
<SYNC Start=940485><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=950095><P Class=ENCC>
Do you have a camp around here?
<SYNC Start=952847><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=954800><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah.
<SYNC Start=957301><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=959271><P Class=ENCC>
Could we possibly<br>come back with you?
<SYNC Start=962073><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=963609><P Class=ENCC>
We've been doing...
<SYNC Start=966577><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=966578><P Class=ENCC>
very badly on our own.
<SYNC Start=969146><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=977456><P Class=ENCC>
I'd have to meet him.
<SYNC Start=979540><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=981359><P Class=ENCC>
I need to ask him some<br>questions, both of you.
<SYNC Start=984361><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=985631><P Class=ENCC>
What questions?
<SYNC Start=988165><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=988166><P Class=ENCC>
Just three.
<SYNC Start=989834><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=989835><P Class=ENCC>
When we get there.
<SYNC Start=991802><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=994139><P Class=ENCC>
You have a gun on you?
<SYNC Start=996140><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=997342><P Class=ENCC>
Can I make sure?
<SYNC Start=999310><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1007269><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah.
<SYNC Start=1009103><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1011990><P Class=ENCC>
Look, I don't know you,
<SYNC Start=1013524><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1013525><P Class=ENCC>
so I'm just gonna<br>tell you this.
<SYNC Start=1016560><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1016561><P Class=ENCC>
You try anything--
<SYNC Start=1019947><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1021733><P Class=ENCC>
anything--
<SYNC Start=1023301><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1025737><P Class=ENCC>
you're gonna be<br>the one who loses.
<SYNC Start=1028272><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1029775><P Class=ENCC>
I don't have<br>anything else to lose.
<SYNC Start=1032577><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1034012><P Class=ENCC>
No.
<SYNC Start=1036681><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1036682><P Class=ENCC>
You do.
<SYNC Start=1038933><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1043272><P Class=ENCC>
Go ahead.
<SYNC Start=1044805><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1054816><P Class=ENCC>
( growling )
<SYNC Start=1056150><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1056151><P Class=ENCC>
Child:<br><i>Nick, look over here.</i>
<SYNC Start=1058069><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1058070><P Class=ENCC>
Child #2:<br><i>This one's Wayne.</i>
<SYNC Start=1060204><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1060205><P Class=ENCC>
- Nick.<br>- Nick, over here.
<SYNC Start=1061439><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1061440><P Class=ENCC>
Hi, Nick!
<SYNC Start=1062773><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1062774><P Class=ENCC>
- Hi, Nick.<br>- Carl: You're naming them?
<SYNC Start=1064992><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1064993><P Class=ENCC>
Well, one of them<br>has a name tag,
<SYNC Start=1067378><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1067379><P Class=ENCC>
so we thought<br>all of them should.
<SYNC Start=1070181><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1070182><P Class=ENCC>
They had names when they were alive.<br>They're dead now.
<SYNC Start=1072717><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1072718><P Class=ENCC>
No, they're not.<br>They're just different.
<SYNC Start=1075186><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1075187><P Class=ENCC>
What the hell<br>are you talking about?
<SYNC Start=1076671><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1076672><P Class=ENCC>
Okay, they don't talk.
<SYNC Start=1078789><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1078790><P Class=ENCC>
They don't think.<br>They eat people.
<SYNC Start=1081759><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1081760><P Class=ENCC>
They kill people.
<SYNC Start=1083260><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1083261><P Class=ENCC>
People kill people.<br>They still have names.
<SYNC Start=1085363><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1085364><P Class=ENCC>
Have you seen what happens?
<SYNC Start=1087298><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1087299><P Class=ENCC>
Have you seen someone<br>die like that?
<SYNC Start=1089500><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1089501><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah, I have.
<SYNC Start=1093304><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1093305><P Class=ENCC>
They're not people<br>and they're not pets.
<SYNC Start=1096507><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1096508><P Class=ENCC>
Don't name them.
<SYNC Start=1098809><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1100145><P Class=ENCC>
We're supposed to go read.<br>Come on.
<SYNC Start=1102246><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1107219><P Class=ENCC>
You coming to<br>story time tonight?
<SYNC Start=1109053><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1109054><P Class=ENCC>
Uh, yeah.
<SYNC Start=1112123><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1112124><P Class=ENCC>
See you then.
<SYNC Start=1113341><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1115544><P Class=ENCC>
I go sometimes.<br>I'm immature.
<SYNC Start=1119180><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1119181><P Class=ENCC>
You wouldn't dig it.<br>It's for kids.
<SYNC Start=1121716><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1123518><P Class=ENCC>
I'm gonna head up there, too.
<SYNC Start=1125469><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1125470><P Class=ENCC>
I'll catch you later,<br>young sir.
<SYNC Start=1127388><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1127389><P Class=ENCC>
Yep.
<SYNC Start=1129339><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1129340><P Class=ENCC>
Army came in<br>and put these fences up.
<SYNC Start=1131475><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1131476><P Class=ENCC>
Made it a place<br>for the people to go.
<SYNC Start=1133477><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1133478><P Class=ENCC>
Last week when we<br>spotted this place,
<SYNC Start=1135613><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1135614><P Class=ENCC>
there was a bunch of walkers<br>behind this chain-link
<SYNC Start=1138149><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1138150><P Class=ENCC>
keeping people out<br>like a bunch of guard dogs.
<SYNC Start=1141485><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1141486><P Class=ENCC>
<i>( music blaring over radio )</i>
<SYNC Start=1143020><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1143021><P Class=ENCC>
So they all just left?
<SYNC Start=1144622><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1144623><P Class=ENCC>
Give a listen.
<SYNC Start=1146524><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1146525><P Class=ENCC>
( music continues playing )
<SYNC Start=1148542><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1148543><P Class=ENCC>
You drew 'em out.
<SYNC Start=1150461><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1150462><P Class=ENCC>
Put a boom box out there<br>three days ago.
<SYNC Start=1152296><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1152297><P Class=ENCC>
Hooked it up<br>to two car batteries.
<SYNC Start=1154498><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1154499><P Class=ENCC>
All right, let's make a sweep.
<SYNC Start=1157468><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1157469><P Class=ENCC>
Make sure it's safe.<br>Grab what you can.
<SYNC Start=1159670><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1159671><P Class=ENCC>
We'll come back tomorrow<br>with more people.
<SYNC Start=1161205><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1177622><P Class=ENCC>
Come on.
<SYNC Start=1179323><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1184796><P Class=ENCC>
( pounding )
<SYNC Start=1187081><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1187082><P Class=ENCC>
Just give it a second.
<SYNC Start=1189200><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1192621><P Class=ENCC>
Okay, I think I got it.
<SYNC Start=1194571><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1195874><P Class=ENCC>
Got what?
<SYNC Start=1197842><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1197843><P Class=ENCC>
I've been trying to guess what<br>Daryl did before the turn.
<SYNC Start=1201345><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1201346><P Class=ENCC>
He's been trying to guess<br>for, like, six weeks.
<SYNC Start=1203431><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1203432><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah, I'm pacing myself.
<SYNC Start=1205415><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1205416><P Class=ENCC>
One shot a day.
<SYNC Start=1207384><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1207385><P Class=ENCC>
All right, shoot.
<SYNC Start=1209386><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1211773><P Class=ENCC>
Well, the way you are<br>at the prison,
<SYNC Start=1214775><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1214776><P Class=ENCC>
you being on the council,<br>you're able to track,
<SYNC Start=1217611><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1217612><P Class=ENCC>
you're helping people, but<br>you're still being kind of...
<SYNC Start=1220815><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1222117><P Class=ENCC>
surly.
<SYNC Start=1223267><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1224903><P Class=ENCC>
Big swing here.
<SYNC Start=1226487><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1228540><P Class=ENCC>
Homicide cop.
<SYNC Start=1229957><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1229958><P Class=ENCC>
( laughing )
<SYNC Start=1231625><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1232627><P Class=ENCC>
What's so funny?
<SYNC Start=1234245><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1234246><P Class=ENCC>
Nothing.<br>It makes perfect sense.
<SYNC Start=1237381><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1237382><P Class=ENCC>
Actually, the man's right.
<SYNC Start=1239616><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1239617><P Class=ENCC>
Undercover.
<SYNC Start=1241502><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1242787><P Class=ENCC>
- Come on, really?<br>- Yep.
<SYNC Start=1245622><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1245623><P Class=ENCC>
I don't like to talk about it
<SYNC Start=1247391><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1247392><P Class=ENCC>
'cause it was a lot<br>of heavy shit, you know?
<SYNC Start=1250427><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1253265><P Class=ENCC>
Dude, come on, really?
<SYNC Start=1255266><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1257969><P Class=ENCC>
( clears throat )
<SYNC Start=1259236><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1259237><P Class=ENCC>
Okay. I'll just keep<br>guessing, I guess.
<SYNC Start=1261872><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1261873><P Class=ENCC>
- Yeah, you keep doing that.<br>- Mm-hmm.
<SYNC Start=1263607><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1263608><P Class=ENCC>
( snarling )
<SYNC Start=1265642><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1265643><P Class=ENCC>
- We're gonna do this, Detective?<br>- Let's do it.
<SYNC Start=1267978><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1269781><P Class=ENCC>
<i>( doors open )</i>
<SYNC Start=1270981><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1273368><P Class=ENCC>
All right, we go in, stay<br>in formation for the sweep.
<SYNC Start=1276754><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1276755><P Class=ENCC>
After that, you all know what<br>you're supposed to look for.
<SYNC Start=1278622><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1278623><P Class=ENCC>
Any questions?
<SYNC Start=1280207><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1280208><P Class=ENCC>
Was there ever a time that<br>you weren't the boss of me?
<SYNC Start=1282126><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1282127><P Class=ENCC>
You had a few years<br>before I was born.
<SYNC Start=1283627><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1303565><P Class=ENCC>
( growling )
<SYNC Start=1306567><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1320134><P Class=ENCC>
<i>( birds chirping )</i>
<SYNC Start=1323203><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1323204><P Class=ENCC>
We were going<br>to Puerto Vallarta
<SYNC Start=1326540><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1326541><P Class=ENCC>
for our honeymoon.
<SYNC Start=1328675><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1328676><P Class=ENCC>
When they shut down<br>the airports,
<SYNC Start=1331612><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1331613><P Class=ENCC>
our connecting flight<br>never connected.
<SYNC Start=1334514><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1335950><P Class=ENCC>
They wouldn't let us<br>leave the terminal, so...
<SYNC Start=1338752><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1340221><P Class=ENCC>
we slept next to these huge
<SYNC Start=1343523><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1343524><P Class=ENCC>
marble sculptures<br>from Zimbabwe.
<SYNC Start=1346593><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1348262><P Class=ENCC>
Then, on the fourth night,
<SYNC Start=1351298><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1351299><P Class=ENCC>
the things just came through.
<SYNC Start=1354801><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1354802><P Class=ENCC>
There were a lot of us and...
<SYNC Start=1357054><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1358539><P Class=ENCC>
now it's just Eddie and me.
<SYNC Start=1360807><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1362376><P Class=ENCC>
And I wouldn't have made it
<SYNC Start=1364511><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1364512><P Class=ENCC>
if it wasn't for him.
<SYNC Start=1366596><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1368182><P Class=ENCC>
And it isn't that...
<SYNC Start=1369883><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1372236><P Class=ENCC>
he saved me over and over again
<SYNC Start=1376823><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1376824><P Class=ENCC>
or that he showed me the things
<SYNC Start=1379443><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1379444><P Class=ENCC>
that I had to do or...
<SYNC Start=1382663><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1382664><P Class=ENCC>
to be willing to do.
<SYNC Start=1384698><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1386868><P Class=ENCC>
If he wasn't still here...
<SYNC Start=1389503><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1389504><P Class=ENCC>
I-- I couldn't be.
<SYNC Start=1392706><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1394175><P Class=ENCC>
I just-- I couldn't.
<SYNC Start=1396910><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1398212><P Class=ENCC>
What were they?
<SYNC Start=1400130><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1400131><P Class=ENCC>
What?
<SYNC Start=1401682><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1403217><P Class=ENCC>
The things you had<br>to be willing to do?
<SYNC Start=1406253><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1406254><P Class=ENCC>
Um...
<SYNC Start=1408088><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1408089><P Class=ENCC>
eating whatever<br>we could find--
<SYNC Start=1411441><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1411442><P Class=ENCC>
animal carcasses
<SYNC Start=1413760><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1413761><P Class=ENCC>
and rotten fruit-- and...
<SYNC Start=1416763><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1418199><P Class=ENCC>
<i>leaving people behind.</i>
<SYNC Start=1420617><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1423154><P Class=ENCC>
Hiding from people<br>who needed my help.
<SYNC Start=1426289><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1428326><P Class=ENCC>
Unlike you.
<SYNC Start=1430327><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1435333><P Class=ENCC>
This is not charity.
<SYNC Start=1437167><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1437168><P Class=ENCC>
You have to have numbers.
<SYNC Start=1439219><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1439220><P Class=ENCC>
People are the best<br>defense against walkers
<SYNC Start=1442055><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1442056><P Class=ENCC>
or people.
<SYNC Start=1444174><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1444175><P Class=ENCC>
We help each other.
<SYNC Start=1445959><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1447311><P Class=ENCC>
You call them "walkers"?
<SYNC Start=1449563><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1545743><P Class=ENCC>
( yelling )
<SYNC Start=1547611><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1547612><P Class=ENCC>
( growling )
<SYNC Start=1549863><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1563761><P Class=ENCC>
You all right?<br>You cut or something?
<SYNC Start=1565578><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1565579><P Class=ENCC>
No, man, but my foot is caught.
<SYNC Start=1567747><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1567748><P Class=ENCC>
All right. He's just caught.<br>Come on, help me up.
<SYNC Start=1570600><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1570601><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- What happened? - Everyone's all right.</i><br><i>We're over in wine and beer.</i>
<SYNC Start=1573303><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1578492><P Class=ENCC>
( roof creaking )
<SYNC Start=1580443><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1580444><P Class=ENCC>
I was moving fast, man.<br>I drove right into the drinks.
<SYNC Start=1583596><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1583597><P Class=ENCC>
Man, you lucked out. If this thing had<br>come down on you the wrong way...
<SYNC Start=1586800><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1597628><P Class=ENCC>
( snarling )
<SYNC Start=1599913><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1599914><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah, uh, we should<br>probably go now.
<SYNC Start=1602115><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1602116><P Class=ENCC>
Bob's still stuck.<br>Get him out of there.
<SYNC Start=1603833><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1603834><P Class=ENCC>
We'll get the others.
<SYNC Start=1605502><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1623154><P Class=ENCC>
Hey!
<SYNC Start=1624521><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1631111><P Class=ENCC>
I saw those sculptures<br>at the airport once.
<SYNC Start=1635281><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1635282><P Class=ENCC>
My favorite was the kids<br>playing leapfrog.
<SYNC Start=1638218><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1640054><P Class=ENCC>
Mine, too.
<SYNC Start=1642188><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1644225><P Class=ENCC>
What Eddie and I had to do,
<SYNC Start=1647093><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1647094><P Class=ENCC>
did you do things like that?
<SYNC Start=1649646><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1653067><P Class=ENCC>
Did you?
<SYNC Start=1654901><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1658939><P Class=ENCC>
Do you think you get<br>to come back from them?
<SYNC Start=1661241><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1664111><P Class=ENCC>
I hope so.
<SYNC Start=1666746><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1666747><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah?
<SYNC Start=1668448><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1668449><P Class=ENCC>
I hope we answer<br>your three questions
<SYNC Start=1671284><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1671285><P Class=ENCC>
to your satisfaction.
<SYNC Start=1673286><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1675489><P Class=ENCC>
( growling )
<SYNC Start=1676823><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1690387><P Class=ENCC>
( grunting )
<SYNC Start=1692806><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1692807><P Class=ENCC>
( snarling )
<SYNC Start=1695892><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1701615><P Class=ENCC>
( grunting )
<SYNC Start=1704067><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1720551><P Class=ENCC>
( machine-gun gunfire )
<SYNC Start=1723503><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1723504><P Class=ENCC>
( clicks )
<SYNC Start=1725305><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1743941><P Class=ENCC>
Hey!
<SYNC Start=1746242><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1746243><P Class=ENCC>
( growling )
<SYNC Start=1748328><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1750614><P Class=ENCC>
Hey!
<SYNC Start=1752248><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1780227><P Class=ENCC>
Daryl, go!
<SYNC Start=1781311><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1794825><P Class=ENCC>
( gunfire )
<SYNC Start=1797627><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1797628><P Class=ENCC>
Let's get Bob.
<SYNC Start=1799662><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1806954><P Class=ENCC>
- ( grunting )<br>- Bob: More, more.
<SYNC Start=1808338><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1808339><P Class=ENCC>
Come on, time to go.
<SYNC Start=1810340><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1810341><P Class=ENCC>
Let's go, now!<br>Come on! Go!
<SYNC Start=1812959><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1812960><P Class=ENCC>
- <i>Let's get out of here!</i><br><i>- Ah!</i>
<SYNC Start=1815061><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1816013><P Class=ENCC>
( shouting )
<SYNC Start=1817797><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1819800><P Class=ENCC>
( screaming )
<SYNC Start=1822986><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1822987><P Class=ENCC>
- Zack!<br>- ( screaming )
<SYNC Start=1825355><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1828826><P Class=ENCC>
Go, go!
<SYNC Start=1829859><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1831328><P Class=ENCC>
Come on!
<SYNC Start=1833446><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1838869><P Class=ENCC>
It's just ahead.
<SYNC Start=1840870><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1843324><P Class=ENCC>
Eddie.
<SYNC Start=1845008><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1845009><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, thank God<br>you're still here.
<SYNC Start=1849128><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1849129><P Class=ENCC>
This is Rick.
<SYNC Start=1850797><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1850798><P Class=ENCC>
<i>He's gonna help us.</i>
<SYNC Start=1853016><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1855402><P Class=ENCC>
Everything's gonna be okay.
<SYNC Start=1858104><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1858105><P Class=ENCC>
Everything--<br>( breathing heavily )
<SYNC Start=1861340><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1865178><P Class=ENCC>
- <i>( blade scrapes )</i><br><i>- ( shouting )</i>
<SYNC Start=1867080><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1868449><P Class=ENCC>
Damn it!
<SYNC Start=1870400><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1870401><P Class=ENCC>
<i>( sobbing )</i>
<SYNC Start=1872518><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1875406><P Class=ENCC>
I wanted to take the boar.
<SYNC Start=1877657><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1877658><P Class=ENCC>
I just knew-- I knew I'd get<br>you here so much quicker.
<SYNC Start=1881361><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1883464><P Class=ENCC>
He's starving.
<SYNC Start=1885798><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1885799><P Class=ENCC>
He's slowing.<br>He needs something alive.
<SYNC Start=1889002><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1894441><P Class=ENCC>
Please, I told you,<br>I can't be without him.
<SYNC Start=1898011><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1900914><P Class=ENCC>
And so I kept him.
<SYNC Start=1903049><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1903050><P Class=ENCC>
It was wrong.
<SYNC Start=1905384><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1905385><P Class=ENCC>
( breathing heavily )
<SYNC Start=1908271><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1908272><P Class=ENCC>
I can't do things like this.
<SYNC Start=1910823><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1911992><P Class=ENCC>
And-- and you have to do<br>things like this.
<SYNC Start=1915561><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1915562><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Let me be like him.</i>
<SYNC Start=1917780><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1917781><P Class=ENCC>
Don't stop it.
<SYNC Start=1920333><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1920334><P Class=ENCC>
Don't end it after.
<SYNC Start=1922452><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1922453><P Class=ENCC>
- No.<br>- Let me be with him.
<SYNC Start=1924921><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1926423><P Class=ENCC>
No!
<SYNC Start=1927623><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1927624><P Class=ENCC>
( groans )
<SYNC Start=1930293><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1930294><P Class=ENCC>
( gasping )
<SYNC Start=1932628><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1936100><P Class=ENCC>
( groans )
<SYNC Start=1938468><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1951131><P Class=ENCC>
Hey.
<SYNC Start=1952899><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1962659><P Class=ENCC>
What were...
<SYNC Start=1965411><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1965412><P Class=ENCC>
the questions?
<SYNC Start=1967580><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1969550><P Class=ENCC>
The three questions?
<SYNC Start=1972118><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1974054><P Class=ENCC>
How many walkers<br>have you killed?
<SYNC Start=1976556><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1983296><P Class=ENCC>
Eddie--
<SYNC Start=1984797><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1984798><P Class=ENCC>
Eddie killed--<br>killed them all.
<SYNC Start=1987016><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1988902><P Class=ENCC>
Until...<br>( gasping )
<SYNC Start=1990903><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1995308><P Class=ENCC>
How many people<br>have you killed?
<SYNC Start=1997527><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2002249><P Class=ENCC>
Just me.
<SYNC Start=2004667><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2004668><P Class=ENCC>
Just me.
<SYNC Start=2006419><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2008539><P Class=ENCC>
Why?
<SYNC Start=2010423><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2014795><P Class=ENCC>
<i>( gasping )</i>
<SYNC Start=2017830><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2022502><P Class=ENCC>
You don't--
<SYNC Start=2024170><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2024171><P Class=ENCC>
you don't get to come back.
<SYNC Start=2026722><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2028609><P Class=ENCC>
You don't get to come back
<SYNC Start=2031644><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2031645><P Class=ENCC>
from things.
<SYNC Start=2034397><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2034398><P Class=ENCC>
You don't...
<SYNC Start=2036482><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2036483><P Class=ENCC>
( gasping )
<SYNC Start=2038517><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2065779><P Class=ENCC>
( growling )
<SYNC Start=2068431><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2078423><P Class=ENCC>
"The children fastened their eyes<br>upon their bit of candle
<SYNC Start=2081325><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2081326><P Class=ENCC>
and watched it melt<br>slowly and pitilessly away.
<SYNC Start=2085395><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2085396><P Class=ENCC>
Saw the half inch of wick<br>stand alone at last.
<SYNC Start=2089266><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2089267><P Class=ENCC>
Saw the feeble flame<br>rise and fall.
<SYNC Start=2092002><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2092003><P Class=ENCC>
Climb the thin tower of smoke.
<SYNC Start=2095555><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2095556><P Class=ENCC>
Linger at its top<br>a moment and then..."
<SYNC Start=2099142><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2105566><P Class=ENCC>
Ma'am, should I take watch now?
<SYNC Start=2107183><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2107184><P Class=ENCC>
Yes, Luke, you do that.
<SYNC Start=2109369><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2109370><P Class=ENCC>
Today...
<SYNC Start=2111905><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2111906><P Class=ENCC>
we are talking about knives--<br>how to use them,
<SYNC Start=2115025><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2115026><P Class=ENCC>
how to be safe with them, and<br>how they could save your life.
<SYNC Start=2117628><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2117629><P Class=ENCC>
Patrick: <i>Ma'am,</i><br><i>may I be dismissed?</i>
<SYNC Start=2119079><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2119080><P Class=ENCC>
- What is it?<br>- I'm not feeling very well.
<SYNC Start=2122366><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2122367><P Class=ENCC>
Sometimes you're gonna<br>have to fight through it.
<SYNC Start=2124635><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2124636><P Class=ENCC>
What if you wind up<br>out there alone?
<SYNC Start=2126870><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2126871><P Class=ENCC>
You just give up<br>because you're feeling bad?
<SYNC Start=2129723><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2129724><P Class=ENCC>
No, it's just I don't want<br>to yack on somebody.
<SYNC Start=2134444><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2136147><P Class=ENCC>
Go.
<SYNC Start=2138148><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2142320><P Class=ENCC>
Okay, today we're gonna<br>learn how to hold a knife,
<SYNC Start=2144938><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2144939><P Class=ENCC>
how to stab and slash<br>and where to aim for.
<SYNC Start=2149726><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2154699><P Class=ENCC>
Please, don't tell your father.
<SYNC Start=2157951><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2166477><P Class=ENCC>
( growling )
<SYNC Start=2168945><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2173084><P Class=ENCC>
( growling )
<SYNC Start=2175302><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2222600><P Class=ENCC>
What?
<SYNC Start=2224684><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2226137><P Class=ENCC>
I don't like going<br>out there, either.
<SYNC Start=2228188><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2237314><P Class=ENCC>
( sighs )<br>Daryl's telling Beth.
<SYNC Start=2239983><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2239984><P Class=ENCC>
There's nothing else to do.
<SYNC Start=2242152><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2243538><P Class=ENCC>
I'll go see her.
<SYNC Start=2245455><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2249160><P Class=ENCC>
I'm not pregnant.
<SYNC Start=2251011><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2251012><P Class=ENCC>
- You know?<br>- I know.
<SYNC Start=2253213><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2254599><P Class=ENCC>
- Oh, thank God.<br>- Yeah.
<SYNC Start=2257834><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2257835><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, my God.
<SYNC Start=2259853><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2259854><P Class=ENCC>
I didn't want to,<br>but we could have.
<SYNC Start=2263673><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2265676><P Class=ENCC>
We can have lives here.
<SYNC Start=2267177><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2267178><P Class=ENCC>
How can you say that<br>after today?
<SYNC Start=2271448><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2271449><P Class=ENCC>
After Lori?
<SYNC Start=2273150><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2273151><P Class=ENCC>
Because I don't want to be<br>afraid of being alive.
<SYNC Start=2276186><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2279490><P Class=ENCC>
Being afraid<br>is what's kept us alive.
<SYNC Start=2283193><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2283194><P Class=ENCC>
No.
<SYNC Start=2285796><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2285797><P Class=ENCC>
It's how we kept breathing.
<SYNC Start=2287798><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2295256><P Class=ENCC>
Hey.
<SYNC Start=2296807><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2296808><P Class=ENCC>
Hi.
<SYNC Start=2298758><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2301479><P Class=ENCC>
What is it?
<SYNC Start=2303263><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2303264><P Class=ENCC>
( sighs )
<SYNC Start=2305182><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2305183><P Class=ENCC>
Zack.
<SYNC Start=2307150><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2312223><P Class=ENCC>
Is he dead?
<SYNC Start=2313723><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2322200><P Class=ENCC>
Okay.
<SYNC Start=2324167><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2344388><P Class=ENCC>
What?
<SYNC Start=2345889><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2351646><P Class=ENCC>
I don't cry anymore, Daryl.
<SYNC Start=2353864><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2356284><P Class=ENCC>
I'm just glad I got<br>to know him, you know?
<SYNC Start=2359119><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2359120><P Class=ENCC>
Me, too.
<SYNC Start=2361154><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2363958><P Class=ENCC>
Are you okay?
<SYNC Start=2365441><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2367111><P Class=ENCC>
Just tired of losing<br>people is all.
<SYNC Start=2370213><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2377288><P Class=ENCC>
I'm glad I didn't<br>say good-bye.
<SYNC Start=2379256><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2379257><P Class=ENCC>
I hate good-byes.
<SYNC Start=2382008><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2384896><P Class=ENCC>
Me, too.
<SYNC Start=2386930><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2403948><P Class=ENCC>
You tried to help her.
<SYNC Start=2406166><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2406167><P Class=ENCC>
You couldn't.<br>No one could.
<SYNC Start=2409085><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2409086><P Class=ENCC>
Some people are too far gone.
<SYNC Start=2411988><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2411989><P Class=ENCC>
You're not.
<SYNC Start=2413990><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2413991><P Class=ENCC>
You tried to help her.
<SYNC Start=2415792><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2415793><P Class=ENCC>
How that woman wound up,
<SYNC Start=2417928><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2417929><P Class=ENCC>
I got close to that.
<SYNC Start=2420046><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2422049><P Class=ENCC>
If I lost Carl and Judith,
<SYNC Start=2424017><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2424018><P Class=ENCC>
if I lost this place--
<SYNC Start=2425501><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2425502><P Class=ENCC>
Not then, Rick.<br>Not even then.
<SYNC Start=2428355><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2430341><P Class=ENCC>
You came back.
<SYNC Start=2432842><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2432843><P Class=ENCC>
Your boy came back.
<SYNC Start=2434894><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2436280><P Class=ENCC>
You get to come back.<br>You do.
<SYNC Start=2438698><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2447024><P Class=ENCC>
( sighs )
<SYNC Start=2450193><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2450194><P Class=ENCC>
<i>( coughing )</i>
<SYNC Start=2452195><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2456417><P Class=ENCC>
( coughing )
<SYNC Start=2458468><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2458469><P Class=ENCC>
( breathing heavily )
<SYNC Start=2460804><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2466727><P Class=ENCC>
( coughing )
<SYNC Start=2470513><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2491869><P Class=ENCC>
( coughing )
<SYNC Start=2494287><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2506934><P Class=ENCC>
( panting )
<SYNC Start=2509352><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2554098><P Class=ENCC>
( wheezing )
<SYNC Start=2557067><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2562713><P Class=ENCC>
Sync and corrections by n17t01<br>www.addic7ed.com
<SYNC Start=2565811><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp

</BODY>
</SAMI>
