<SAMI>
<HEAD>
<HEAD>
<TITLE></TITLE>
<STYLE TYPE="text/css">
<!--
P { margin-left:8pt; margin-right:8pt; margin-bottom:2pt; margin-top:2pt;
    text-align:center;
    font-size:20pt; font-family:arial, sans-serif; font-weight:normal; color:white; }
.ENCC { Name:English; lang:en-US; SAMIType:CC;}
#STDPrn { Name:Standard Print;}
#LargePrn { Name:Large Print; font-size:25pt;}
#SmallPrn { Name:Small Print; font-size:15pt;}
-->
</STYLE>
</HEAD>
<BODY>
<SYNC Start=18253><P Class=ENCC>
Please.<br>You don't have to do this.
<SYNC Start=21780><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=21890><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, God!
<SYNC Start=24620><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=24726><P Class=ENCC>
Not like this.<br>No, you can't. Please!
<SYNC Start=28184><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=31366><P Class=ENCC>
No.
<SYNC Start=33527><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=35203><P Class=ENCC>
Please.
<SYNC Start=36693><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=39408><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Por favor!</i>
<SYNC Start=41308><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=41410><P Class=ENCC>
I am so sorry.
<SYNC Start=43469><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=43578><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, God, I wanna go home!
<SYNC Start=46342><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=186988><P Class=ENCC>
You having fun?
<SYNC Start=188979><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=189090><P Class=ENCC>
- Am I the only one having a problem with this?<br>- I guess they're used to it.
<SYNC Start=193117><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=193228><P Class=ENCC>
<i>I just keep thinking about<br>how far we must be from a hospital.</i>
<SYNC Start=196288><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=196398><P Class=ENCC>
<i>You know, with doctors who operate<br>instead of amputate?</i>
<SYNC Start=199492><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=199601><P Class=ENCC>
So dramatic.
<SYNC Start=201831><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=204306><P Class=ENCC>
- Would you slow the fuck down!<br>- Jesus Christ, relax! You're such a tourist.
<SYNC Start=208470><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=208577><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Por favor!</i>
<SYNC Start=211045><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=211146><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Calm down. He drives through it every day.<br>I think he knows how to drive better than you do.</i>
<SYNC Start=214912><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=215016><P Class=ENCC>
- He drives like a fucking lunatic.<br>- Well, we're fine, aren't we?
<SYNC Start=218179><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=218286><P Class=ENCC>
I can't believe I let you talk me into this.
<SYNC Start=221483><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=221590><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- We're flying back.<br>- Okay, fine.</i>
<SYNC Start=223558><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=223658><P Class=ENCC>
- And I'm picking the hotels from now on.<br>- You were right about that.
<SYNC Start=226559><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=226661><P Class=ENCC>
I'm sorry.
<SYNC Start=228595><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=238840><P Class=ENCC>
Check it out.
<SYNC Start=240535><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=240642><P Class=ENCC>
- That looks painful.<br>- Stop it!
<SYNC Start=242610><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=242711><P Class=ENCC>
What do you think it says?
<SYNC Start=245111><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=245213><P Class=ENCC>
It says,<br>"Welcome to Brazil. Now bend over."
<SYNC Start=247738><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=247849><P Class=ENCC>
- We have to remember that.<br>- He likes you.
<SYNC Start=250409><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=296531><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Deus!</i>
<SYNC Start=299125><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=299234><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Jesus Christ! Stay on the road, you lunatic!</i>
<SYNC Start=301998><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=309577><P Class=ENCC>
Go out the window!<br>Go! Go!
<SYNC Start=312307><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=312414><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Get out!<br>- Get out! Go, go, go!</i>
<SYNC Start=315906><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=316017><P Class=ENCC>
Get out right now!
<SYNC Start=318315><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=318420><P Class=ENCC>
Everybody out!
<SYNC Start=321617><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=325060><P Class=ENCC>
- Whoa. Whoa.<br>- Go!
<SYNC Start=327961><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=328063><P Class=ENCC>
Go! Get off!
<SYNC Start=330361><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=330465><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Jump! Get off!</i>
<SYNC Start=332194><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=336271><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, my God.<br>Get off! Get off, get off!
<SYNC Start=339603><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=341242><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Get off!</i>
<SYNC Start=343676><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=357892><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Oh, shit!<br>- Did everyone get out of there?</i>
<SYNC Start=361055><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=365667><P Class=ENCC>
- You still think flying<br>would've been a waste of money?
<SYNC Start=369159><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=369270><P Class=ENCC>
- Don't start.<br>- I told you this was-
<SYNC Start=370828><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=370939><P Class=ENCC>
- Don't!<br>- Fine.
<SYNC Start=372600><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=372707><P Class=ENCC>
Why is my luggage<br>always the last to come out?
<SYNC Start=375198><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=379714><P Class=ENCC>
Ale-Alex? Found it!
<SYNC Start=381944><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=382050><P Class=ENCC>
Great!
<SYNC Start=383950><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=384119><P Class=ENCC>
I'm impressed.
<SYNC Start=385984><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=386087><P Class=ENCC>
- Why?<br>- Bit like bringing sand to the beach though.
<SYNC Start=388681><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=388790><P Class=ENCC>
Bringing a couple of fit little birds<br>like that to Brazil?
<SYNC Start=392191><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=392293><P Class=ENCC>
- That's my sister.<br>- Splendid.
<SYNC Start=395421><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=395530><P Class=ENCC>
Just like to know me options.
<SYNC Start=397828><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=397932><P Class=ENCC>
It's not an option.
<SYNC Start=400059><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=400168><P Class=ENCC>
- Get everything?<br>- Yeah, I think so.
<SYNC Start=402329><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=402437><P Class=ENCC>
- Hi, I'm Finn. Nice to meet you.<br>- Bea. You too.
<SYNC Start=404667><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=404773><P Class=ENCC>
- Liam.<br>- Hi. How are you guys?
<SYNC Start=407333><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=407442><P Class=ENCC>
Good as gold.<br>Hi. I'm Finn.
<SYNC Start=409603><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=409711><P Class=ENCC>
- Amy. Nice to meet you.<br>- Liam.
<SYNC Start=412111><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=412213><P Class=ENCC>
Guess we're bonded for life now, eh?<br>Near-death experience.
<SYNC Start=415580><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=415683><P Class=ENCC>
- Great story to tell the grandkids.<br>- Yeah.
<SYNC Start=418117><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=418219><P Class=ENCC>
- You think they got a plan to get us out of here?<br>- I doubt it.
<SYNC Start=421279><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=421389><P Class=ENCC>
- Should find out, I suppose.<br>- I'll find out.
<SYNC Start=423357><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=423458><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, man.
<SYNC Start=425926><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=434302><P Class=ENCC>
"Bussie!"<br>You suck at driving buses!
<SYNC Start=437100><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=437205><P Class=ENCC>
You should do something else.
<SYNC Start=439298><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=439407><P Class=ENCC>
Pick bananas or something.
<SYNC Start=441170><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=441276><P Class=ENCC>
- Hey.<br>- Hi.
<SYNC Start=443301><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=444412><P Class=ENCC>
- I'm Alex.<br>- Pru.
<SYNC Start=446312><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=446414><P Class=ENCC>
Yes. Yes.
<SYNC Start=448314><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=448416><P Class=ENCC>
- You're, um, supposed to kiss back.<br>- Ah. Sorry.
<SYNC Start=451214><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=452687><P Class=ENCC>
Except you don't actually kiss.<br>You sort of kiss the air.
<SYNC Start=455087><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=455190><P Class=ENCC>
- Yeah. Start again.<br>- I'm Alex.
<SYNC Start=456919><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=457025><P Class=ENCC>
- Pru. Hi. Nice to meet you.<br>- Nice to meet you.
<SYNC Start=459585><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=459694><P Class=ENCC>
- So, do you speak Spanish?<br>- It's Portuguese here.
<SYNC Start=461662><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=461763><P Class=ENCC>
- Right. So, any idea what<br>these guys are talking about?<br>- Another bus is on its way.
<SYNC Start=465130><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=465233><P Class=ENCC>
- It's gonna be about 10 hours.<br>- Ten hours?
<SYNC Start=468100><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=468203><P Class=ENCC>
- Yeah. And then it's another 18 to Recife.<br>- Wait, what did you just say?
<SYNC Start=470797><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=470905><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- About what?<br>- About where we're headed.</i>
<SYNC Start=472805><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=472907><P Class=ENCC>
Well, the way that guy was driving,<br>I'm not really sure.
<SYNC Start=475899><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=476010><P Class=ENCC>
- But you said Recife, right?<br>- Yeah.
<SYNC Start=477671><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=477779><P Class=ENCC>
- Which is north of Salvador.<br>- On most maps.
<SYNC Start=480145><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=480248><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Which means we've been<br>headed north this whole time.<br>- Idiots, the pair of us.</i>
<SYNC Start=483513><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=483618><P Class=ENCC>
We got on the wrong fucking bus!
<SYNC Start=485950><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=486054><P Class=ENCC>
- The Rastafarian.<br>- I knew he was dodgy.
<SYNC Start=487646><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=487755><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Brilliant cunts we are.<br>- Wait. Where did you guys think you were going?</i>
<SYNC Start=490849><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=490959><P Class=ENCC>
- To Floripa.<br>- Oh, you took the long way.
<SYNC Start=493519><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=493628><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Yeah. Where was this bus headed?<br>- Bel?.</i>
<SYNC Start=495687><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=495797><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Don't suppose that Bel? is famous<br>for having a 10-to-1 ratio of women to men...</i>
<SYNC Start=499699><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=499801><P Class=ENCC>
where even the ugly girls<br>look like Giselle.
<SYNC Start=501735><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=501836><P Class=ENCC>
<i>And they're all smart, fun,<br>alcoholic nymphomaniacs...</i>
<SYNC Start=504896><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=505006><P Class=ENCC>
with a soft spot for charming<br>if slightly grubby foreign tourists?
<SYNC Start=507338><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=507442><P Class=ENCC>
Uh, not that I'm aware of, no.
<SYNC Start=509910><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=510011><P Class=ENCC>
- Too bad.<br>- 'Cause Floripa is.
<SYNC Start=511911><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=512013><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Six- Six Sports Illustrated<br>swimsuit models are from Floripa.</i>
<SYNC Start=515380><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=515483><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Do you understand how select<br>that gene pool must be?<br>- It's a tiny town.</i>
<SYNC Start=518816><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=530098><P Class=ENCC>
- Leave it out.<br>- All right.
<SYNC Start=532225><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=532333><P Class=ENCC>
- Hey, are you getting anything?<br>- No. Nothing.
<SYNC Start=535166><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=537939><P Class=ENCC>
Do you think they know<br>something we don't?
<SYNC Start=540737><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=540842><P Class=ENCC>
I'm gonna walk around.
<SYNC Start=542776><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=548850><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Bonita.</i>
<SYNC Start=550977><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=551085><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Meu nome ?Bea.</i>
<SYNC Start=554248><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=554355><P Class=ENCC>
Hey!
<SYNC Start=556823><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=556925><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Hey! Hey!</i>
<SYNC Start=561021><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=561129><P Class=ENCC>
Photograph.<br>Photograph. It's a-
<SYNC Start=562687><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=566100><P Class=ENCC>
Hey, hey.
<SYNC Start=567965><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=568069><P Class=ENCC>
- Jesus! Calm down!<br>- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
<SYNC Start=571038><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=571139><P Class=ENCC>
Calm down! I'm sorry!
<SYNC Start=573767><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=573875><P Class=ENCC>
- You're not to take pictures<br>of kids without permission.<br>- How am I supposed to know?
<SYNC Start=577106><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=577211><P Class=ENCC>
Hey. "No, senhorita"<br>would have been fine.
<SYNC Start=580374><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=580481><P Class=ENCC>
Or even "No, you stupid,<br>bloody gringo!"
<SYNC Start=582381><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=582483><P Class=ENCC>
Asshole! I can't hear ya!
<SYNC Start=584815><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=584919><P Class=ENCC>
Leave the girl alone. All right?
<SYNC Start=588480><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=590425><P Class=ENCC>
Prick.
<SYNC Start=592325><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=592427><P Class=ENCC>
Tabloids have been writing stories<br>about foreigners...
<SYNC Start=594327><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=594429><P Class=ENCC>
coming here to steal kids<br>to sell their organs for transplants.
<SYNC Start=597023><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=597131><P Class=ENCC>
It's created a lot of hostility<br>to tourists.
<SYNC Start=599156><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=599267><P Class=ENCC>
- Has that anything to do with<br>that couple that were missing?<br>- I don't think they're a couple.
<SYNC Start=602725><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=602837><P Class=ENCC>
- French couple, right?<br>- Oh, I thought you meant the kayakers.
<SYNC Start=605670><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=605773><P Class=ENCC>
Oi! We got no designs on your organs!<br>All right? Your kidneys are safe with us!
<SYNC Start=609903><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=610011><P Class=ENCC>
We're on holiday, for fuck's sake!
<SYNC Start=611911><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=612013><P Class=ENCC>
Hey, where'd you get those from?
<SYNC Start=615039><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=621189><P Class=ENCC>
- What did she say?<br>- She said there's a bar on the<br>beach and it's really close.
<SYNC Start=624352><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=624459><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- We can walk.<br>- Is there a town?</i>
<SYNC Start=626359><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=626461><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Don't you think we should wait for the next bus?<br>- They haven't made the next bus.</i>
<SYNC Start=629988><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=634636><P Class=ENCC>
Let's go.<br>We'll come back later.
<SYNC Start=637196><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=637305><P Class=ENCC>
Let's do it.
<SYNC Start=639205><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=642310><P Class=ENCC>
So, how did you end up here?
<SYNC Start=644540><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=644646><P Class=ENCC>
I'm here with my little sister.
<SYNC Start=647046><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=647148><P Class=ENCC>
She's always wanted<br>to come to Brazil...
<SYNC Start=649048><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=649150><P Class=ENCC>
my mom didn't want her to go alone<br>and didn't trust her with Amy...
<SYNC Start=652711><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=652820><P Class=ENCC>
so I get to pretend to be the boyfriend<br>when creepy guys try to bother her.
<SYNC Start=656221><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=656324><P Class=ENCC>
What happens when<br>creepy girls bother you?
<SYNC Start=659225><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=659327><P Class=ENCC>
- So what about you? You traveling alone?<br>- Yeah.
<SYNC Start=662455><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=662563><P Class=ENCC>
- That's brave.<br>- Not really. I've been everywhere<br>they tell you not to go.
<SYNC Start=665726><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=665833><P Class=ENCC>
Colombia, Nigeria. Just spent<br>three months in a favela in Rocinha.
<SYNC Start=670236><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=670338><P Class=ENCC>
The only place I've ever had any problems<br>is in a small town in Australia.
<SYNC Start=673796><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=673908><P Class=ENCC>
- So, you're from Australia?<br>- Uh-huh.
<SYNC Start=676468><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=676577><P Class=ENCC>
Got a boyfriend in Australia?
<SYNC Start=678477><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=678579><P Class=ENCC>
No! You did not just say that!
<SYNC Start=681480><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=681582><P Class=ENCC>
- What?<br>- "So, you got a boyfriend in Australia?"
<SYNC Start=684380><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=684485><P Class=ENCC>
I just meant that if I had a girlfriend<br>or a little sister who was traveling alone...
<SYNC Start=688717><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=688823><P Class=ENCC>
I'd be a little worried, that's all.
<SYNC Start=690723><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=690825><P Class=ENCC>
Well, don't be.<br>I can take care of myself.
<SYNC Start=693794><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=693895><P Class=ENCC>
- So, did she say this was<br>a proper bar with real drinks?
<SYNC Start=697456><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=697565><P Class=ENCC>
I don't know.<br>She didn't say.
<SYNC Start=699795><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=699901><P Class=ENCC>
Christ, I'd do anything for a pint.
<SYNC Start=702392><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=702503><P Class=ENCC>
I'd lick the sweat<br>off a monkey's balls.
<SYNC Start=705404><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=705506><P Class=ENCC>
"I'd lick the sweat off a monkey's balls."
<SYNC Start=708839><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=708943><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Christ on a cracker.<br>- This is amazing!</i>
<SYNC Start=711639><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=711746><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Oh, yes! Check this out!</i>
<SYNC Start=715182><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=720655><P Class=ENCC>
- Baby!<br>- Oh, yes!
<SYNC Start=722850><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=722957><P Class=ENCC>
Whoo! Who wants to go for a swim?
<SYNC Start=725323><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=725426><P Class=ENCC>
- Yeah, sure!<br>- Yes! This is what I was talking about.
<SYNC Start=728327><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=728429><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- They got beer?<br>- Get your kit off, girls!</i>
<SYNC Start=731125><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=731232><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Come on!<br>Let's swim!</i>
<SYNC Start=733132><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=734869><P Class=ENCC>
Shit.
<SYNC Start=737303><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=737405><P Class=ENCC>
I left my top in Rio.<br>Would you guys mind if I went topless?
<SYNC Start=740863><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=740975><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Are you serious? No. Keep your shirt on.<br>- Yeah. Why not?</i>
<SYNC Start=744536><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=744645><P Class=ENCC>
Do you see what they're wearing, Alex?<br>We're not in America.
<SYNC Start=747614><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=747715><P Class=ENCC>
<i>No one's gonna care if I go topless.</i>
<SYNC Start=750479><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=750585><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah, but the idea is to tastefully reveal<br>as much as possible-
<SYNC Start=754715><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=754822><P Class=ENCC>
Oi, oi.<br>Get a load of that.
<SYNC Start=757382><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=757492><P Class=ENCC>
without actually<br>revealing so much...
<SYNC Start=759960><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=760061><P Class=ENCC>
that you can still get into heaven.
<SYNC Start=763292><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=765133><P Class=ENCC>
That was good.
<SYNC Start=766657><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=766768><P Class=ENCC>
Yes!
<SYNC Start=769635><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=769737><P Class=ENCC>
- That is a fantastic trick.<br>- Well, it's still a Catholic country.
<SYNC Start=772865><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=772974><P Class=ENCC>
- Well, we're Catholics.<br>- And we definitely don't mind.
<SYNC Start=775306><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=775409><P Class=ENCC>
<i>No. In fact, I think I can speak for Liam when<br>I say we wouldn't be offended in the slightest.</i>
<SYNC Start=780608><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=780715><P Class=ENCC>
<i>In fact, let's all go topless,<br>boys and girls.</i>
<SYNC Start=783479><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=783584><P Class=ENCC>
No, Amy-
<SYNC Start=785916><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=786020><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Oh! Nice!</i>
<SYNC Start=788921><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=789023><P Class=ENCC>
Put your shirt on.
<SYNC Start=790923><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=791025><P Class=ENCC>
She's a naughty girl.
<SYNC Start=792754><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=792860><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- How about that? Is this better?<br>- Oh, no!</i>
<SYNC Start=795886><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=795997><P Class=ENCC>
Come on.<br>Let's go.
<SYNC Start=797555><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=797665><P Class=ENCC>
All right, let's go get it wet.
<SYNC Start=799724><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=804505><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Come on, Alex!<br>- Whoo!</i>
<SYNC Start=807736><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=832033><P Class=ENCC>
Let's get a drink.
<SYNC Start=833933><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=834035><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Alex, where are you going?<br>- Over here.</i>
<SYNC Start=836435><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=836537><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Whoo!</i>
<SYNC Start=839301><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=847181><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Qual ?seu nome?<br>- ?camila.</i>
<SYNC Start=849115><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=849217><P Class=ENCC>
Pru. Alex.
<SYNC Start=851208><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=851319><P Class=ENCC>
Nice to meet you.
<SYNC Start=853844><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=853955><P Class=ENCC>
- What do you want?<br>- Uh, Coke, please.
<SYNC Start=856685><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=856791><P Class=ENCC>
A Coke? You're 7,000 miles away<br>from home. Try something new.
<SYNC Start=859692><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=859794><P Class=ENCC>
- Like what?<br>- Have you ever had assai?
<SYNC Start=861694><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=861796><P Class=ENCC>
Uh, no.
<SYNC Start=863388><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=863497><P Class=ENCC>
It's, like, this amazing drink<br>from the Amazon. It's-
<SYNC Start=866466><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=866567><P Class=ENCC>
Just a Coke's fine.<br>Thank you. No ice.
<SYNC Start=869536><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=869637><P Class=ENCC>
My God, I love this country.
<SYNC Start=871969><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=872073><P Class=ENCC>
<i>It's like we died on the bus and this is heaven.</i>
<SYNC Start=875042><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=875142><P Class=ENCC>
<i>It's heaven.<br>It's, uh, para?o.</i>
<SYNC Start=877303><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=877411><P Class=ENCC>
And you? Angel.
<SYNC Start=879777><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=880815><P Class=ENCC>
Wait.
<SYNC Start=883545><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=883651><P Class=ENCC>
You too!<br>Come on!
<SYNC Start=885551><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=885653><P Class=ENCC>
Ah!
<SYNC Start=887917><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=889056><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Don't want to-<br>- Por favor?</i>
<SYNC Start=890921><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=893828><P Class=ENCC>
- No ice.<br>- No, no. It's, like, a hundred fucking degrees.
<SYNC Start=896228><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=896330><P Class=ENCC>
No, it's like ordering with dysentery<br>or without dysentery. No ice.
<SYNC Start=898924><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=899033><P Class=ENCC>
Dysentery.
<SYNC Start=900227><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=900401><P Class=ENCC>
This is unbelievable.
<SYNC Start=903768><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=903871><P Class=ENCC>
You think you've found<br>your own private Shangri-la.
<SYNC Start=906931><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=907041><P Class=ENCC>
Next thing you know, the place is crawling<br>with backpacking tourists wearing sandals.
<SYNC Start=910477><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=910578><P Class=ENCC>
Welcome to paradise.<br>I'm Svend.
<SYNC Start=912876><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=912980><P Class=ENCC>
- Pru, my sister Bea, Amy.<br>- Hi.
<SYNC Start=914777><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=914882><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Where are you from?<br>- London.</i>
<SYNC Start=917316><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=917418><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- London. We're from Sweden.<br>- Sweden! Nice!</i>
<SYNC Start=919818><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=919921><P Class=ENCC>
We rode this beauty all the way from Mexico City<br>and stopped to have a drink three days ago.
<SYNC Start=925382><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=925493><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Now we can't<br>find any reason to leave.</i>
<SYNC Start=927893><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=927995><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah, and Brazilians<br>are the warmest and friendliest...
<SYNC Start=930555><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=930665><P Class=ENCC>
and most chill people<br>you're ever gonna meet.
<SYNC Start=933259><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=933367><P Class=ENCC>
<i>The drinks are cheap, and Camila's cooking,<br>it's unbelievable.</i>
<SYNC Start=937963><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=938072><P Class=ENCC>
And you even have a barrack you can sleep in<br>on the beach- only four bucks a night.
<SYNC Start=941906><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=942009><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Oh, my God.<br>- Go on!</i>
<SYNC Start=943909><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=944011><P Class=ENCC>
About what?
<SYNC Start=945911><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=946013><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, no, no.<br>It's just an expression, like "no way."
<SYNC Start=948846><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=948950><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Oh. Yeah!<br>- I hate living up to the natives' stereotype, but-</i>
<SYNC Start=952886><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=952987><P Class=ENCC>
and I think I speak for<br>my brother when I say this-
<SYNC Start=955547><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=955656><P Class=ENCC>
we're not leaving here...
<SYNC Start=957556><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=957658><P Class=ENCC>
- until either we run out of money-<br>- Or they run out of beer!
<SYNC Start=961059><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=963064><P Class=ENCC>
- Oh, my God.<br>- So, what do you think?
<SYNC Start=965532><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=965633><P Class=ENCC>
About getting on the bus?<br>Come on. Look where we are.
<SYNC Start=968761><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=968869><P Class=ENCC>
Well, how do we get back?
<SYNC Start=970769><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=970871><P Class=ENCC>
Hitchhike to a bigger town. We'll get on<br>a better bus, with air conditioning and brakes.
<SYNC Start=974034><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=976310><P Class=ENCC>
You in?
<SYNC Start=978210><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=978312><P Class=ENCC>
- Sure.<br>- Yeah! Let's do it!
<SYNC Start=980212><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=980314><P Class=ENCC>
All right, fuck the bus.
<SYNC Start=981975><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=984418><P Class=ENCC>
Yes!
<SYNC Start=986318><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=989924><P Class=ENCC>
Ow.
<SYNC Start=992552><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1005272><P Class=ENCC>
Camila.
<SYNC Start=1007934><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1017718><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Da. Ciao.<br>- Ciao.</i>
<SYNC Start=1020243><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1021288><P Class=ENCC>
Whoo! Let's go!<br>Let's go, let's go!
<SYNC Start=1024257><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1024358><P Class=ENCC>
- Amy! Amy!<br>- Come on! In the middle!
<SYNC Start=1026553><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1026660><P Class=ENCC>
Ohh! Nice!
<SYNC Start=1029060><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1029163><P Class=ENCC>
Why won't someone pass me the ball?
<SYNC Start=1031927><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1034702><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Come on, come on!<br>- Think fast!</i>
<SYNC Start=1037569><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1037671><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Oh!</i>
<SYNC Start=1039730><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1039840><P Class=ENCC>
<i>We know how to play this game!</i>
<SYNC Start=1042775><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1042877><P Class=ENCC>
- Ohh!<br>- You okay?
<SYNC Start=1044777><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1044879><P Class=ENCC>
- You suck, Amy.<br>- Let's go!
<SYNC Start=1046813><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1046914><P Class=ENCC>
You're on our side, Alex!
<SYNC Start=1049314><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1052720><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Come on, Alex! Pass!</i>
<SYNC Start=1054620><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1058859><P Class=ENCC>
Yes! Whoo-hoo!
<SYNC Start=1060952><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1061062><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Come on, Liam! Run! Run!</i>
<SYNC Start=1064122><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1064231><P Class=ENCC>
- Hi.<br>- Hi.
<SYNC Start=1066131><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1066233><P Class=ENCC>
I am study the English.
<SYNC Start=1068633><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1068736><P Class=ENCC>
- Okay.<br>- Okay?
<SYNC Start=1070636><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1070738><P Class=ENCC>
- Uh, I-I think I make my "practions" on you.<br>- Sure. Yes.
<SYNC Start=1074936><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1075042><P Class=ENCC>
- So, what's your name?<br>- Uh, Pru.
<SYNC Start=1077169><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1077278><P Class=ENCC>
- Pru?<br>- Yes.
<SYNC Start=1079178><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1079280><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- And what is your name?<br>- My name is Kiko. Meu nome ?Kiko.</i>
<SYNC Start=1082181><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1082283><P Class=ENCC>
- Nice to meet you.<br>- Nice to meet you.
<SYNC Start=1085081><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1085186><P Class=ENCC>
Okay, Pru, how many<br>brothers and sisters are you havin'?
<SYNC Start=1089145><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1089256><P Class=ENCC>
Uh, only child.
<SYNC Start=1091156><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1091258><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Que?<br>- Sorry. Zero. Zero. None.</i>
<SYNC Start=1093658><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1093761><P Class=ENCC>
Zero?
<SYNC Start=1095661><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1095763><P Class=ENCC>
- Right.<br>- Ah. Only child.
<SYNC Start=1097663><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1097765><P Class=ENCC>
- Only child.<br>- Ah. Zero.
<SYNC Start=1099596><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1099700><P Class=ENCC>
I'm havin' four brothers<br>and two sisters.
<SYNC Start=1102601><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1102703><P Class=ENCC>
- Wow. Big family.<br>- Big family.
<SYNC Start=1106002><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1106107><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Uma fam?ia grande.<br>- Fam?ia grande.</i>
<SYNC Start=1109372><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1109477><P Class=ENCC>
Hey, my man!<br>What's your name?
<SYNC Start=1112446><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1112546><P Class=ENCC>
- Alex.<br>- Okay, Alex. I'm love you, America!
<SYNC Start=1116676><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1116784><P Class=ENCC>
I love you, Brazil!
<SYNC Start=1118684><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1118786><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah! How many brothers<br>and sisters are you having?
<SYNC Start=1122278><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1122389><P Class=ENCC>
<i>No, it's how many brothers and sisters<br>do you have?</i>
<SYNC Start=1125290><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1125392><P Class=ENCC>
No, no, no, no, no.<br>I'm havin' four brothers and two sisters.
<SYNC Start=1129158><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1129263><P Class=ENCC>
How many brothers and sisters<br>are you having?
<SYNC Start=1132164><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1132266><P Class=ENCC>
- Do you have- No- One.<br>- One?
<SYNC Start=1134166><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1134268><P Class=ENCC>
One sister. Yeah.<br>Uh, Bea! Bea.
<SYNC Start=1137567><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1137671><P Class=ENCC>
- This is my sister, Bea.<br>- Hi!
<SYNC Start=1140299><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1140407><P Class=ENCC>
And this is her friend, Amy.
<SYNC Start=1143205><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1143310><P Class=ENCC>
- Just beautiful.<br>- Kiko.
<SYNC Start=1145642><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1145746><P Class=ENCC>
- Thank you.<br>- E-Easy, Kiko.
<SYNC Start=1148044><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1148149><P Class=ENCC>
- Nice to meet you.<br>- Hi. How are you?
<SYNC Start=1150913><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1152286><P Class=ENCC>
We're gonna go get a drink.
<SYNC Start=1154982><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1199133><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Yeah!</i>
<SYNC Start=1201033><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1201135><P Class=ENCC>
One more. Go!
<SYNC Start=1202796><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1202903><P Class=ENCC>
Right!<br>Has everybody got one?
<SYNC Start=1204734><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1204838><P Class=ENCC>
One! Two! Three! Cheers!
<SYNC Start=1207932><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1208042><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah!
<SYNC Start=1211136><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1213414><P Class=ENCC>
Oi!
<SYNC Start=1215143><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1215249><P Class=ENCC>
Ugh!
<SYNC Start=1217149><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1217251><P Class=ENCC>
Cacha?, baby!<br>Cheers!
<SYNC Start=1219481><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1219587><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Oh! That's disgusting! I love it!</i>
<SYNC Start=1221817><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1221922><P Class=ENCC>
Oh! Oh! Stop! Stop! Stop!<br>Stop! Stop!
<SYNC Start=1224755><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1224858><P Class=ENCC>
My music!<br>My music!
<SYNC Start=1226826><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1226927><P Class=ENCC>
You like dancing?
<SYNC Start=1228485><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1228596><P Class=ENCC>
- Yeah.<br>- Come here, girl.
<SYNC Start=1231258><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1232600><P Class=ENCC>
Come on, Amy!
<SYNC Start=1234830><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1238072><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah!
<SYNC Start=1241098><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1252786><P Class=ENCC>
What, dance?<br>No, no, no.
<SYNC Start=1254686><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1254788><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Go on. Dance with her.</i>
<SYNC Start=1256653><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1256757><P Class=ENCC>
No, no, I'm not dancing.
<SYNC Start=1260090><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1260194><P Class=ENCC>
No, no, no, it's not you. It's just that I have<br>these very European hips.
<SYNC Start=1264255><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1264365><P Class=ENCC>
- They have to stay parallel to the floor at all times.<br>- Huh?
<SYNC Start=1267528><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1267635><P Class=ENCC>
Apart from when I'm naked.
<SYNC Start=1270103><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1270204><P Class=ENCC>
I can't do that.
<SYNC Start=1272866><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1272973><P Class=ENCC>
You're not gonna take no<br>for an answer, are you?
<SYNC Start=1275134><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1275242><P Class=ENCC>
Go on!<br>Show her how it's done!
<SYNC Start=1277836><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1283117><P Class=ENCC>
Look at him go!
<SYNC Start=1285085><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1293894><P Class=ENCC>
Hi.
<SYNC Start=1295862><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1299600><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah!
<SYNC Start=1302068><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1306907><P Class=ENCC>
Hey. Where are you going?
<SYNC Start=1309000><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1311779><P Class=ENCC>
Hey, my man!<br>My man!
<SYNC Start=1314407><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1315449><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Ol?<br>- Ol?</i>
<SYNC Start=1317349><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1317451><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Uh, que ?seu nome?</i>
<SYNC Start=1319351><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1319453><P Class=ENCC>
- Arolea.<br>- Areola?
<SYNC Start=1321683><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1321789><P Class=ENCC>
Arolea!
<SYNC Start=1323689><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1323791><P Class=ENCC>
Aroayla.
<SYNC Start=1325691><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1325793><P Class=ENCC>
A... ro... lea.
<SYNC Start=1328660><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1328762><P Class=ENCC>
Arolea.
<SYNC Start=1330662><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1330764><P Class=ENCC>
Yes!
<SYNC Start=1332664><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1332766><P Class=ENCC>
I get a kiss just for<br>saying your name?
<SYNC Start=1336065><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1336170><P Class=ENCC>
Arolea.
<SYNC Start=1338161><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1338272><P Class=ENCC>
Arolea.<br>Mmm!
<SYNC Start=1340934><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1341041><P Class=ENCC>
Mmm!
<SYNC Start=1342941><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1371572><P Class=ENCC>
<i>This song is so nasty.</i>
<SYNC Start=1373472><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1373574><P Class=ENCC>
What are they saying?
<SYNC Start=1375474><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1375576><P Class=ENCC>
I'm not getting it all,<br>but basically...
<SYNC Start=1377476><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1377578><P Class=ENCC>
it's a long list of explicit things<br>he likes to do in his car-
<SYNC Start=1380479><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1380581><P Class=ENCC>
one being up the ass.
<SYNC Start=1382913><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1383016><P Class=ENCC>
Mmm!
<SYNC Start=1384916><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1400134><P Class=ENCC>
Do you wanna dance?
<SYNC Start=1402102><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1402202><P Class=ENCC>
- Yes.<br>- Come on. Let's dance.
<SYNC Start=1404170><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1415382><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, yes!
<SYNC Start=1417782><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1420020><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, it's like that, is it? Oh!
<SYNC Start=1422511><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1422623><P Class=ENCC>
- Yes. I want. Yeah. I like very much.<br>- Mmm.
<SYNC Start=1425353><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1426560><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, God!
<SYNC Start=1428460><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1428562><P Class=ENCC>
- Ah?<br>- Damn!
<SYNC Start=1430621><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1431732><P Class=ENCC>
Yes. More.<br>All of it. All of it.
<SYNC Start=1433700><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1433801><P Class=ENCC>
Oh! Yeah!<br>Take it all off. Yeah!
<SYNC Start=1437862><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1437971><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Mais?<br>- Oh!</i>
<SYNC Start=1440701><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1440808><P Class=ENCC>
Please.
<SYNC Start=1442708><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1442810><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Mais! Mais!</i>
<SYNC Start=1445142><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1446246><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, my God.
<SYNC Start=1449044><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1450617><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, God bless Brazil.<br>Come on.
<SYNC Start=1454644><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1460661><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah!
<SYNC Start=1462390><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1465899><P Class=ENCC>
I love Brazil!
<SYNC Start=1468800><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1473574><P Class=ENCC>
<i>God, you really are an angel.<br>Wanna come back with me to London?</i>
<SYNC Start=1477806><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1480247><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, w-wait. No!<br>It's not like that!
<SYNC Start=1482511><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1482616><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- ?assim.<br>- But I thought you liked me. No?</i>
<SYNC Start=1485608><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1485719><P Class=ENCC>
No.
<SYNC Start=1487710><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1506640><P Class=ENCC>
Hey, Svend!<br>What a night!
<SYNC Start=1509734><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1509843><P Class=ENCC>
Hey! Dude!
<SYNC Start=1512243><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1512346><P Class=ENCC>
Bloody lightweight.
<SYNC Start=1514576><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1574908><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Bea!</i>
<SYNC Start=1576808><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1576910><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Bea, get up!</i>
<SYNC Start=1578810><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1578912><P Class=ENCC>
Come on, get up. Get up.
<SYNC Start=1581073><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1581181><P Class=ENCC>
Bea.<br>Come on, come on.
<SYNC Start=1583149><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1584518><P Class=ENCC>
- You okay?<br>- What?
<SYNC Start=1586918><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1587020><P Class=ENCC>
- You okay?<br>- No. I feel sick.
<SYNC Start=1589955><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1590057><P Class=ENCC>
What happened?
<SYNC Start=1592423><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1592526><P Class=ENCC>
They robbed us.
<SYNC Start=1594391><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1594494><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- What?<br>- We got robbed.</i>
<SYNC Start=1596985><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1597097><P Class=ENCC>
- By who?<br>- I don't know.
<SYNC Start=1599292><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1599399><P Class=ENCC>
- What did they take?<br>- Everything.
<SYNC Start=1601299><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1601401><P Class=ENCC>
- What do you mean, everything?<br>- I mean everything.
<SYNC Start=1603335><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1603437><P Class=ENCC>
Our money, our credit cards,<br>our phones, our backpacks...
<SYNC Start=1606406><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1606506><P Class=ENCC>
our passports, everything.
<SYNC Start=1608406><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1608508><P Class=ENCC>
- Nana's ring.<br>- Yes, everything.
<SYNC Start=1610772><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1612579><P Class=ENCC>
My earrings are gone.<br>How did they take my fucking earrings?
<SYNC Start=1615480><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1615582><P Class=ENCC>
I think that they drugged us. They must have<br>put something in our drinks last night.
<SYNC Start=1619177><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1619286><P Class=ENCC>
Mom is gonna kill me. She told me not to<br>bring the ring, 'cause-
<SYNC Start=1621846><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1621955><P Class=ENCC>
Bea.
<SYNC Start=1624014><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1624124><P Class=ENCC>
That is a very small problem right now.<br>We have no money. We have no way out of here.
<SYNC Start=1628185><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1629229><P Class=ENCC>
We'll be fine.
<SYNC Start=1631094><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1631198><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- You think so?<br>- Yeah.</i>
<SYNC Start=1633029><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1633133><P Class=ENCC>
<i>'Cause I'm not so sure.<br>Come on.</i>
<SYNC Start=1635931><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1710343><P Class=ENCC>
Mm-mmm.
<SYNC Start=1713244><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1713346><P Class=ENCC>
Hold on.
<SYNC Start=1716907><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1737204><P Class=ENCC>
Hey!
<SYNC Start=1739195><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1739306><P Class=ENCC>
No! No! No! No!
<SYNC Start=1741240><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1810944><P Class=ENCC>
No.
<SYNC Start=1812605><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1825091><P Class=ENCC>
No.
<SYNC Start=1828060><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1834167><P Class=ENCC>
What?<br>What did she say?
<SYNC Start=1836067><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1836169><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, God. She's saying it's down here to the left.
<SYNC Start=1839138><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1839239><P Class=ENCC>
The other guy said it's down here<br>to the right. So I have no idea.
<SYNC Start=1842140><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1842242><P Class=ENCC>
Are you sure it's smart<br>going to the police?
<SYNC Start=1844642><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1844744><P Class=ENCC>
- Aren't they supposed to be<br>worse than the criminals?<br>- Not all of them.
<SYNC Start=1847645><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1847747><P Class=ENCC>
- Come on.<br>- Someone in this town<br>must know what's going on.
<SYNC Start=1851046><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1855121><P Class=ENCC>
These kids are definitely in on it.<br>It's freaking me out.
<SYNC Start=1858022><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1866533><P Class=ENCC>
- God.<br>- What did he say?
<SYNC Start=1868865><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1868969><P Class=ENCC>
Let's, uh- Let's just try up here-<br>this little house or something.
<SYNC Start=1872405><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1879346><P Class=ENCC>
- Are you sure we're going the right way?<br>- That's what he said.
<SYNC Start=1882247><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1882349><P Class=ENCC>
I don't know.
<SYNC Start=1884317><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1894728><P Class=ENCC>
Alex?<br>Where are you going?
<SYNC Start=1896696><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1896796><P Class=ENCC>
Aah! Ow.
<SYNC Start=1899196><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1899299><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- What is it?<br>- The Swede's motorcycle.</i>
<SYNC Start=1901927><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1903770><P Class=ENCC>
Hello?
<SYNC Start=1905738><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1907641><P Class=ENCC>
Ol?
<SYNC Start=1909609><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1909709><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Ol?</i>
<SYNC Start=1912041><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1913446><P Class=ENCC>
Hey! Hey!<br>Whose motorcycle is this?
<SYNC Start=1915676><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1915782><P Class=ENCC>
Ask him who got-<br>Where'd they get this motorcycle?
<SYNC Start=1918273><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1920887><P Class=ENCC>
That's Alex's hat.<br>That kid has Alex's hat.
<SYNC Start=1924414><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1924524><P Class=ENCC>
- Alex!<br>- Alex, he's got your hat.
<SYNC Start=1927084><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1929562><P Class=ENCC>
Grab him! Quick!
<SYNC Start=1931393><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1933066><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Wait up, Liam!<br>- Just wanna talk to you!</i>
<SYNC Start=1936502><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1936603><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Where'd you get that hat?</i>
<SYNC Start=1938400><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1938505><P Class=ENCC>
Come back here!
<SYNC Start=1941838><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1941942><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Wait! Shit!</i>
<SYNC Start=1944274><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1945712><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Oww! Aah!</i>
<SYNC Start=1947680><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1950984><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Where'd he go?<br>- Don't know.</i>
<SYNC Start=1953282><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1954721><P Class=ENCC>
Aah!
<SYNC Start=1956848><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1959793><P Class=ENCC>
Come back here!<br>Now!
<SYNC Start=1962762><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1966066><P Class=ENCC>
You wait till I fucking catch you.
<SYNC Start=1969524><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1975775><P Class=ENCC>
Now I've got you, you little shit.
<SYNC Start=1977936><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1980981><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, shit.
<SYNC Start=1982846><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1987287><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, shit. Is he all right?
<SYNC Start=1990256><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1996997><P Class=ENCC>
What happened?<br>What'd you do?
<SYNC Start=1999192><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=1999299><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- It was an accident.<br>- You threw a rock at him?</i>
<SYNC Start=2002200><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2002302><P Class=ENCC>
Didn't mean to hit his head.
<SYNC Start=2004236><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2004337><P Class=ENCC>
- It was an accident.<br>- We got robbed!
<SYNC Start=2006862><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2006973><P Class=ENCC>
He had our friend's cap!
<SYNC Start=2009464><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2009576><P Class=ENCC>
It was an accident!
<SYNC Start=2011476><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2011578><P Class=ENCC>
Hey! Don't touch me!
<SYNC Start=2014012><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2027027><P Class=ENCC>
- Walk away.<br>- Let's just go. Let's just go.
<SYNC Start=2028892><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2028995><P Class=ENCC>
Hey, come on. Just relax.<br>Just walk away.
<SYNC Start=2032089><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2032198><P Class=ENCC>
Come on, come on, come on!
<SYNC Start=2035099><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2040607><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Are they following us?<br>- No, I don't think so.</i>
<SYNC Start=2043508><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2043610><P Class=ENCC>
<i>W-We were robbed.<br>R-Roubado. Roubado.</i>
<SYNC Start=2045601><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2045712><P Class=ENCC>
- I know.<br>- You know?
<SYNC Start=2047612><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2047714><P Class=ENCC>
- Everybody knows.<br>- Who did it?
<SYNC Start=2049614><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2049716><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Who did it?</i>
<SYNC Start=2052617><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2054554><P Class=ENCC>
What police?
<SYNC Start=2056852><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2056956><P Class=ENCC>
You crazy.<br>No police here. Okay?
<SYNC Start=2059356><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2059459><P Class=ENCC>
<i>What do you mean, there's no police here?</i>
<SYNC Start=2062360><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2062462><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Christ, dude, where are you going?<br>- Stay here.</i>
<SYNC Start=2065431><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2069636><P Class=ENCC>
Nice work.
<SYNC Start=2071536><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2071638><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Leave him alone.<br>- It was a fucking accident.</i>
<SYNC Start=2074038><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2074140><P Class=ENCC>
- You don't throw a rock at a kid!<br>- Let it go!
<SYNC Start=2076404><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2076509><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Let it go!<br>- I'm sorry. Okay?</i>
<SYNC Start=2079444><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2079546><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Sorry, everybody.<br>- It's all right.</i>
<SYNC Start=2082242><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2094461><P Class=ENCC>
Let's go, guys.
<SYNC Start=2096429><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2097464><P Class=ENCC>
- Damn!<br>- Come on!
<SYNC Start=2099193><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2099299><P Class=ENCC>
Come on!<br>Come on!
<SYNC Start=2100732><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2100834><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Okay, man! Hold up!<br>- Where are we going?</i>
<SYNC Start=2104463><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2104571><P Class=ENCC>
- Is not good for you in town.<br>- Yeah, no kidding.
<SYNC Start=2107563><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2107674><P Class=ENCC>
They are looking for the father<br>of this boy that you hurt.
<SYNC Start=2110666><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2110777><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Is bad man.</i>
<SYNC Start=2112677><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2112779><P Class=ENCC>
<i>They find him, is very bad for you.<br>Okay?</i>
<SYNC Start=2115441><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2115548><P Class=ENCC>
Ask him where we're going, Pru.
<SYNC Start=2117448><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2121287><P Class=ENCC>
There is-There is<br>a house of his uncle...
<SYNC Start=2124188><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2124290><P Class=ENCC>
<i>and he says that it's very safe<br>for us there.</i>
<SYNC Start=2126690><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2126793><P Class=ENCC>
No. We just want a ride.<br>Do you know anybody with a car?
<SYNC Start=2130194><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2132799><P Class=ENCC>
No, no, no. No car.
<SYNC Start=2135165><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2135268><P Class=ENCC>
There is-
<SYNC Start=2138294><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2138404><P Class=ENCC>
<i>The only car is of the guy<br>that robbed us.</i>
<SYNC Start=2141168><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2141274><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- You'd better wait for the bus.<br>- There's a bus? When is there a bus?</i>
<SYNC Start=2144368><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2144477><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Uh, qu-quando- At what time?</i>
<SYNC Start=2146638><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2146746><P Class=ENCC>
Uh... today?
<SYNC Start=2148646><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2148748><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Today there's a bus?<br>- Yes.</i>
<SYNC Start=2150875><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2150984><P Class=ENCC>
- What time?<br>- Two day.
<SYNC Start=2154647><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2154754><P Class=ENCC>
- Two days.<br>- Two days?
<SYNC Start=2156654><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2156756><P Class=ENCC>
Why does everything take<br>so fucking long in this place?
<SYNC Start=2159224><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2159325><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Two day-<br>- Okay, vamos. Vamos la. Vamos.</i>
<SYNC Start=2162294><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2167567><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Fuck! These insects are eating me alive.</i>
<SYNC Start=2170468><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2170570><P Class=ENCC>
- Look at that. All over me legs.<br>- Leave it out.
<SYNC Start=2173471><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2173573><P Class=ENCC>
There'd better be a big bag<br>of fucking weed at this house.
<SYNC Start=2176872><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2179846><P Class=ENCC>
Kiko, can we just...<br>stop for a minute?
<SYNC Start=2183873><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2183983><P Class=ENCC>
<i>I'll be back in a minute.</i>
<SYNC Start=2186383><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2186486><P Class=ENCC>
- Where are you going?<br>- The men's room.
<SYNC Start=2188977><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2222589><P Class=ENCC>
Whose idea was it to leave the bus?
<SYNC Start=2225149><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2225258><P Class=ENCC>
- Whose idea was it to come to Brazil?<br>- It was yours!
<SYNC Start=2228159><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2228261><P Class=ENCC>
- I wanted to go to Bali.<br>- You're missing the point.
<SYNC Start=2231162><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2231264><P Class=ENCC>
The point is, if we dig deep enough<br>I'm sure we'll discover this is all your fault.
<SYNC Start=2234392><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2234500><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, right. Yeah.
<SYNC Start=2236400><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2236502><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Which'll make me feel a lot better.<br>- Right.</i>
<SYNC Start=2239403><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2239505><P Class=ENCC>
<i>And you know what? I did want to<br>come to Brazil. Why? Because I like girls.</i>
<SYNC Start=2242770><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2242875><P Class=ENCC>
And I like beaches and drinking.
<SYNC Start=2244638><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2244744><P Class=ENCC>
And when they say<br>"Come to Brazil," they say...
<SYNC Start=2246735><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2246846><P Class=ENCC>
"Come to Brazil! We've got girls<br>and beaches and drinking!"
<SYNC Start=2250646><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2250750><P Class=ENCC>
What they do not say,<br>what they completely neglect to mention...
<SYNC Start=2253651><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2253753><P Class=ENCC>
is anything about being chased<br>into the jungle by an angry fuckin' mob...
<SYNC Start=2257120><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2257223><P Class=ENCC>
<i>which is not my idea<br>of a fun vacation at all!</i>
<SYNC Start=2260124><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2260226><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Oi, Kiko!<br>How far is this house?</i>
<SYNC Start=2262660><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2262762><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Uh, uh, como far?<br>- Hey, man, not so bad.</i>
<SYNC Start=2266459><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2266566><P Class=ENCC>
What do you mean?<br>This is pretty fucking bad!
<SYNC Start=2269160><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2269269><P Class=ENCC>
<i>What about a road?<br>Is there a road we can walk on?</i>
<SYNC Start=2271931><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2272038><P Class=ENCC>
- No roads.<br>- What kind of house has no roads?
<SYNC Start=2275303><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2277410><P Class=ENCC>
Fucking hell.
<SYNC Start=2280436><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2403669><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Come on! Almost there!</i>
<SYNC Start=2405569><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2405671><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Kiko! Where are we going?</i>
<SYNC Start=2408071><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2408174><P Class=ENCC>
<i>There is a place where we can rest.</i>
<SYNC Start=2411075><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2411177><P Class=ENCC>
<i>This place is amazing.</i>
<SYNC Start=2413145><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2414847><P Class=ENCC>
Check it out!
<SYNC Start=2416747><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2416849><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Come on! I show you something.</i>
<SYNC Start=2418749><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2418851><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Wow.<br>- This is my secret place.</i>
<SYNC Start=2421820><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2421921><P Class=ENCC>
Kiko, can we swim here?
<SYNC Start=2423821><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2423923><P Class=ENCC>
I show you some caves.
<SYNC Start=2425823><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2425925><P Class=ENCC>
What caves? Where?
<SYNC Start=2427825><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2427927><P Class=ENCC>
There are caves in the water.
<SYNC Start=2430327><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2430430><P Class=ENCC>
We'll swim, then go to house.
<SYNC Start=2432330><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2432432><P Class=ENCC>
- How close is the house?<br>- It's right on the river.
<SYNC Start=2435629><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2435735><P Class=ENCC>
Ten minutes.
<SYNC Start=2438033><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2438137><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Hey, guys, watch me!</i>
<SYNC Start=2440571><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2440673><P Class=ENCC>
You're joking. You're never gonna jump off of this!
<SYNC Start=2443540><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2443643><P Class=ENCC>
- Kiko, It's too dangerous.<br>- Go ahead!
<SYNC Start=2446271><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2446379><P Class=ENCC>
- Stop encouraging him!<br>- I am diving all the time!
<SYNC Start=2448870><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2448981><P Class=ENCC>
Less talking!<br>More action!
<SYNC Start=2451472><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2451584><P Class=ENCC>
No, stop!<br>Don't do it! No!
<SYNC Start=2453575><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2453686><P Class=ENCC>
Kiko! Whoa!
<SYNC Start=2456484><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2458624><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Crazy son of a bitch!</i>
<SYNC Start=2461218><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2461327><P Class=ENCC>
- You're gonna kill yourself!<br>- Come on!
<SYNC Start=2465024><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2465131><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Come on, come on! Come down!</i>
<SYNC Start=2467691><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2467800><P Class=ENCC>
Swim!<br>I show you caves!
<SYNC Start=2470360><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2470470><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- No way I'm doing that!<br>- Come on. Let's go see 'em.</i>
<SYNC Start=2473234><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2473339><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- I'm staying here.<br>- You sure?</i>
<SYNC Start=2475671><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2475775><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Come on! Come on!</i>
<SYNC Start=2477675><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2477777><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- You can do it!<br>- Yeah, I'm gonna, uh, stay here too.</i>
<SYNC Start=2480405><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2480513><P Class=ENCC>
Right.<br>Behave yourself.
<SYNC Start=2482811><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2489088><P Class=ENCC>
Here?
<SYNC Start=2490988><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2491090><P Class=ENCC>
- The caves! Come on!<br>- Over there?
<SYNC Start=2493285><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2493392><P Class=ENCC>
I can't.<br>No, no, I can't.
<SYNC Start=2495292><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2495394><P Class=ENCC>
Follow me.<br>It's an easy swim.
<SYNC Start=2497089><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2497196><P Class=ENCC>
You can do it.
<SYNC Start=2499096><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2499198><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Come on. Let's do it.<br>- Okay.</i>
<SYNC Start=2502167><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2517817><P Class=ENCC>
- Hey, Bea, you okay?<br>- Yeah.
<SYNC Start=2520547><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2520653><P Class=ENCC>
- Is this it?<br>- Come on. A little more far.
<SYNC Start=2524555><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2529762><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Follow me.<br>- Kiko, where are we?</i>
<SYNC Start=2533254><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2533366><P Class=ENCC>
Where are we goin'?
<SYNC Start=2535266><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2535368><P Class=ENCC>
Fuck! That was a bat!
<SYNC Start=2537302><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2538671><P Class=ENCC>
Kiko.
<SYNC Start=2540400><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2540506><P Class=ENCC>
Come on, guys.<br>Let's go.
<SYNC Start=2542406><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2542508><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Kiko, what is this?<br>- We go under.</i>
<SYNC Start=2545602><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2545711><P Class=ENCC>
- No!<br>- No. No.
<SYNC Start=2547508><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2547613><P Class=ENCC>
- There-There is a hole.<br>- No, no, no, no.
<SYNC Start=2549513><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2549615><P Class=ENCC>
Hey, man, it's easy.
<SYNC Start=2552049><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2552151><P Class=ENCC>
This is incredible.<br>Incredible!
<SYNC Start=2554676><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2554787><P Class=ENCC>
- All right. Let's go. Fine. Fine.<br>- No. No.
<SYNC Start=2557312><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2557423><P Class=ENCC>
- One, two, three.<br>- What?
<SYNC Start=2560153><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2596996><P Class=ENCC>
Asshole!<br>What the fuck is this?
<SYNC Start=2600090><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2601701><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, Jesus!
<SYNC Start=2603794><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2603903><P Class=ENCC>
That was not easy.<br>It was scary.
<SYNC Start=2606804><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2606906><P Class=ENCC>
And this is not incredible.
<SYNC Start=2608806><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2608908><P Class=ENCC>
We go more.<br>We go more.
<SYNC Start=2610808><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2610910><P Class=ENCC>
Ow! Ow!<br>Jesus!
<SYNC Start=2612810><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2612912><P Class=ENCC>
- Kiko!<br>- Fucking lunatic!
<SYNC Start=2615244><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2616415><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Kiko!<br>- Shit! The light!</i>
<SYNC Start=2618474><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2653819><P Class=ENCC>
Holy shit!
<SYNC Start=2656117><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2656222><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Wow, look at this place.<br>Bea, look at this.</i>
<SYNC Start=2659191><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2660960><P Class=ENCC>
Wow, this is amazing. What is this place?
<SYNC Start=2663520><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2663629><P Class=ENCC>
Very nice, Kiko!
<SYNC Start=2665529><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2665631><P Class=ENCC>
<i>This water is so beautiful!</i>
<SYNC Start=2668031><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2676542><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- This is incredible.<br>- Yes.</i>
<SYNC Start=2678567><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2680680><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Is my secret place.</i>
<SYNC Start=2683114><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2693359><P Class=ENCC>
I-I never making friends<br>with the gringos before.
<SYNC Start=2697352><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2697463><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- No?<br>- No.</i>
<SYNC Start=2699090><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2699198><P Class=ENCC>
I never have, um, speak with one.
<SYNC Start=2701496><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2701600><P Class=ENCC>
Really?
<SYNC Start=2703500><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2703602><P Class=ENCC>
Well, hi there!
<SYNC Start=2705467><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2705571><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, my God.
<SYNC Start=2707539><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2711544><P Class=ENCC>
You okay?
<SYNC Start=2713444><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2713546><P Class=ENCC>
What?
<SYNC Start=2715104><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2715214><P Class=ENCC>
You-You feel okay?
<SYNC Start=2716977><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2717083><P Class=ENCC>
- Yes, yes. I am okay.<br>- Okay.
<SYNC Start=2719779><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2721053><P Class=ENCC>
Uh, maybe...
<SYNC Start=2722816><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2722922><P Class=ENCC>
we go back to town.
<SYNC Start=2724822><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2724924><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- What?<br>- Aqui. Yes.</i>
<SYNC Start=2726653><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2726759><P Class=ENCC>
Is better we go back.
<SYNC Start=2728522><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2728627><P Class=ENCC>
We just hiked 10 hours through the jungle.<br>How can you go back?
<SYNC Start=2732028><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2732131><P Class=ENCC>
- Did you say go back?<br>- We're not going back. No way.
<SYNC Start=2735123><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2735234><P Class=ENCC>
Yes.<br>I-I-I think is better.
<SYNC Start=2738567><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2738671><P Class=ENCC>
- Why?<br>- Maybe I talk with these guys, okay?
<SYNC Start=2742129><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2742241><P Class=ENCC>
Um, tell them you are okay.
<SYNC Start=2745039><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2745144><P Class=ENCC>
Maybe find a ride for you.
<SYNC Start=2747305><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2747413><P Class=ENCC>
But why are you saying this now?
<SYNC Start=2749847><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2749949><P Class=ENCC>
- I don't know. It's just, um-<br>- It's just what?
<SYNC Start=2753680><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2753786><P Class=ENCC>
No- No nothing.
<SYNC Start=2755686><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2755788><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Look, it's simple- 10 hours hike through<br>the jungle, or 10 minutes to the house.</i>
<SYNC Start=2759383><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2759492><P Class=ENCC>
I don't like hiking.<br>We go to the fucking house.
<SYNC Start=2762256><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2762361><P Class=ENCC>
Is there a problem<br>with this house, Kiko?
<SYNC Start=2765330><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2765431><P Class=ENCC>
No. No problem.
<SYNC Start=2766989><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2767099><P Class=ENCC>
Then we go to the house.<br>Okay?
<SYNC Start=2769624><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2769735><P Class=ENCC>
- Okay.<br>- Okay.
<SYNC Start=2771896><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2772004><P Class=ENCC>
That's for almost killing us!
<SYNC Start=2774268><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2776542><P Class=ENCC>
Come on, guys.<br>We walk back.
<SYNC Start=2778908><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2786752><P Class=ENCC>
- Oh. Hey. What's going on?<br>- Oi, oi!
<SYNC Start=2790188><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2790289><P Class=ENCC>
Hi. How was it?
<SYNC Start=2793452><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2793559><P Class=ENCC>
- Awesome. Underwater caves. It was cool.<br>- There were bats.
<SYNC Start=2796460><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2796562><P Class=ENCC>
Come on.<br>Let's go together.
<SYNC Start=2798462><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2798564><P Class=ENCC>
Hey, Kiko, show me how you do that.
<SYNC Start=2800794><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2800900><P Class=ENCC>
- I wanna do it. Show me. Yeah.<br>- Let's jump together.
<SYNC Start=2803733><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2803836><P Class=ENCC>
One, two, three!
<SYNC Start=2806270><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2812845><P Class=ENCC>
You guys should try it!
<SYNC Start=2815279><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2815381><P Class=ENCC>
Dude, I wanna try.<br>Show me how you do it.
<SYNC Start=2818179><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2818284><P Class=ENCC>
Okay, okay.<br>I go.
<SYNC Start=2820252><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2821353><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Whoo! Crazy!</i>
<SYNC Start=2824151><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2826559><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Whoo! Oh!</i>
<SYNC Start=2829756><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2832832><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Shit! He's bleeding!<br>- Kiko!</i>
<SYNC Start=2834732><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2834834><P Class=ENCC>
- We're coming down!<br>- Stay up!
<SYNC Start=2836734><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2836836><P Class=ENCC>
Jesus Christ!
<SYNC Start=2838394><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2840005><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- What happened?<br>- He must have hit his head on a rock below.</i>
<SYNC Start=2843338><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2843442><P Class=ENCC>
Keep his head above the water!
<SYNC Start=2845410><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2845511><P Class=ENCC>
Is he conscious?
<SYNC Start=2848309><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2848414><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, my God.
<SYNC Start=2850609><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2850716><P Class=ENCC>
- Get him to the side.<br>- Come on, come on!
<SYNC Start=2853241><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2853352><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Swim! Swim!<br>- Over here!</i>
<SYNC Start=2855115><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2858357><P Class=ENCC>
What are we gonna do?
<SYNC Start=2860018><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2860125><P Class=ENCC>
Take him back to the village.
<SYNC Start=2862025><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2862127><P Class=ENCC>
We'll never get back before dark.<br>We'll go to the house.
<SYNC Start=2864493><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2864597><P Class=ENCC>
- We don't know where the house is!<br>- He said it was on the river.
<SYNC Start=2867498><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2867600><P Class=ENCC>
Help me get him out. Grab my shirt.<br>We're gonna wrap his head.
<SYNC Start=2870262><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2873239><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Is he gonna die?</i>
<SYNC Start=2875139><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2875241><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- No.<br>- How do you know?</i>
<SYNC Start=2877141><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2877243><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Between rugby and bar fights, I've probably<br>had a concussion a year since I was nine.</i>
<SYNC Start=2881145><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2881247><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- When did you play rugby?<br>- I played!</i>
<SYNC Start=2883647><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2883749><P Class=ENCC>
- We should have just gone back to the village.<br>- No way!
<SYNC Start=2886183><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2886285><P Class=ENCC>
They'll fucking kill us!
<SYNC Start=2888253><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2890923><P Class=ENCC>
What is this place doing here?
<SYNC Start=2893323><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2893425><P Class=ENCC>
You okay?
<SYNC Start=2895325><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2895427><P Class=ENCC>
He all right?
<SYNC Start=2897895><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2899398><P Class=ENCC>
Hello!
<SYNC Start=2901298><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2901400><P Class=ENCC>
Nearly there.
<SYNC Start=2903595><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2903702><P Class=ENCC>
Whoa. This is crazy.
<SYNC Start=2905602><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2905704><P Class=ENCC>
Almost there.
<SYNC Start=2907604><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2907706><P Class=ENCC>
Hello?
<SYNC Start=2909674><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2910776><P Class=ENCC>
This guy likes his privacy.
<SYNC Start=2912676><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2912778><P Class=ENCC>
- Hey, look, there's a dip there.<br>- Hello!
<SYNC Start=2916009><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2916115><P Class=ENCC>
Oi!
<SYNC Start=2918015><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2918117><P Class=ENCC>
Anyone home?
<SYNC Start=2921018><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2921120><P Class=ENCC>
Bea, get a chair.
<SYNC Start=2923213><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2925624><P Class=ENCC>
Here we go.
<SYNC Start=2928457><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2938170><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Fuck!</i>
<SYNC Start=2940798><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2942908><P Class=ENCC>
- Oh, shit, that's deep.<br>- Jesus.
<SYNC Start=2945741><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2945844><P Class=ENCC>
Keep pressure on that.<br>We need something to close this up.
<SYNC Start=2949280><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2949381><P Class=ENCC>
Find, uh, superglue,<br>needle and thread, anything.
<SYNC Start=2952748><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2952851><P Class=ENCC>
Check upstairs.
<SYNC Start=2954546><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2964863><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Ol?</i>
<SYNC Start=2966831><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=2977776><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Ol?</i>
<SYNC Start=2979744><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3013712><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Ol?</i>
<SYNC Start=3015680><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3044443><P Class=ENCC>
- Hold his head right here.<br>I gotta cut some of this out.<br>- Okay.
<SYNC Start=3047674><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3047780><P Class=ENCC>
Oh. Sorry.
<SYNC Start=3049680><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3049782><P Class=ENCC>
- Hold his fucking head up!<br>- I got it. I got it!
<SYNC Start=3052512><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3054253><P Class=ENCC>
Vicodin, codeine, Demerol made out to<br>every imaginable name and nationality-
<SYNC Start=3058155><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3058257><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Gustav Roth, Marco Terelli-<br>- Hold him.</i>
<SYNC Start=3061090><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3061193><P Class=ENCC>
What the hell is this place, some kind of<br>youth hostel for drug addicts?
<SYNC Start=3064253><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3064363><P Class=ENCC>
- Gotta hold this shut.<br>- I got it!
<SYNC Start=3066263><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3066365><P Class=ENCC>
- A stapler?<br>- No, no, no. You can't use that.
<SYNC Start=3068265><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3068367><P Class=ENCC>
- It's fine.<br>- No!
<SYNC Start=3070335><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3070436><P Class=ENCC>
It's what they used on me when I split<br>me head open. Hold it closed.
<SYNC Start=3072870><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3072971><P Class=ENCC>
- Hold it shut.<br>- You got it.
<SYNC Start=3074598><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3074706><P Class=ENCC>
- Oh, Jesus.<br>- More.
<SYNC Start=3076230><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3076341><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Oh, shit!</i>
<SYNC Start=3077706><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3077810><P Class=ENCC>
- Sorry, mate.<br>- Hold him.
<SYNC Start=3080074><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3082781><P Class=ENCC>
- Okay?<br>- I got him. I got him.
<SYNC Start=3085443><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3088520><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Kiko, where you going? Are you okay?</i>
<SYNC Start=3092183><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3092291><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Kiko.<br>- Kiko, you okay?</i>
<SYNC Start=3094919><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3099798><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Kiko.</i>
<SYNC Start=3102562><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3102668><P Class=ENCC>
Should we keep him awake?
<SYNC Start=3104761><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3104870><P Class=ENCC>
I don't know.
<SYNC Start=3106770><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3106872><P Class=ENCC>
He could have a concussion.
<SYNC Start=3109238><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3115481><P Class=ENCC>
Clothes.
<SYNC Start=3117381><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3123822><P Class=ENCC>
Mmm.<br>Smoked herring.
<SYNC Start=3125722><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3127826><P Class=ENCC>
Let's see.<br>Mushrooms and cheese.
<SYNC Start=3129885><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3129995><P Class=ENCC>
That's good.
<SYNC Start=3132395><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3134533><P Class=ENCC>
Hey. Look. Look what I got.
<SYNC Start=3137434><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3137536><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, you want some, don't you?
<SYNC Start=3139436><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3139538><P Class=ENCC>
You want some.<br>Come here. Up here.
<SYNC Start=3141938><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3142040><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah.
<SYNC Start=3144008><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3145210><P Class=ENCC>
Nasty.<br>Here you go.
<SYNC Start=3147440><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3148480><P Class=ENCC>
Ohh.
<SYNC Start=3150243><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3152184><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah!
<SYNC Start=3154982><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3161760><P Class=ENCC>
Hey.
<SYNC Start=3163728><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3165964><P Class=ENCC>
- Anything good?<br>- I think our luck might be turning.
<SYNC Start=3169229><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3169334><P Class=ENCC>
- Oh, yeah?<br>- Twenty-year-old single malt.
<SYNC Start=3172792><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3178010><P Class=ENCC>
What the hell is this?
<SYNC Start=3179978><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3189621><P Class=ENCC>
Who the hell are these people?
<SYNC Start=3192089><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3200332><P Class=ENCC>
Hmm.
<SYNC Start=3201993><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3202100><P Class=ENCC>
Thank you.
<SYNC Start=3204398><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3285751><P Class=ENCC>
This house is so fucking creepy.
<SYNC Start=3288151><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3288253><P Class=ENCC>
We'll just stay the night.
<SYNC Start=3290153><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3290255><P Class=ENCC>
Then Kiko will show us the way out<br>in the morning.
<SYNC Start=3293156><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3293258><P Class=ENCC>
- If he dies, how do we get back?<br>- He's not gonna die.
<SYNC Start=3296659><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3296762><P Class=ENCC>
'Cause I don't wanna be here<br>if his uncle shows up and we're like...
<SYNC Start=3299663><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3299765><P Class=ENCC>
"Hello, mate. Here's your dead nephew.<br>And you're out of scotch."
<SYNC Start=3302666><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3306772><P Class=ENCC>
And why is there no road?<br>What kind of fucking hermit lives-
<SYNC Start=3309673><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3309775><P Class=ENCC>
- Oi!<br>- Yeah, I know. Leave it out.
<SYNC Start=3312903><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3315147><P Class=ENCC>
So, how does this rank<br>with your other trips?
<SYNC Start=3318048><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3318150><P Class=ENCC>
After the last few days,<br>right at the bottom. You?
<SYNC Start=3321051><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3321153><P Class=ENCC>
- Well, we had a pretty tough time in Cambodia.<br>- At least we had that hash.
<SYNC Start=3324953><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3325057><P Class=ENCC>
Yeah, and those Dutch girls.
<SYNC Start=3327025><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3328727><P Class=ENCC>
I just want to go home.
<SYNC Start=3330695><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3455754><P Class=ENCC>
His uncle.
<SYNC Start=3457722><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3466998><P Class=ENCC>
What's going on?
<SYNC Start=3468898><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3469000><P Class=ENCC>
I'm not sure.
<SYNC Start=3470627><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3488186><P Class=ENCC>
What is he saying?
<SYNC Start=3490313><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3503301><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Alex.</i>
<SYNC Start=3505360><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3509274><P Class=ENCC>
Kiko, what's-
<SYNC Start=3510969><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3511076><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Ol?</i>
<SYNC Start=3512976><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3520519><P Class=ENCC>
Hi.
<SYNC Start=3522487><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3522587><P Class=ENCC>
Hi.
<SYNC Start=3524487><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3524589><P Class=ENCC>
- You guys American?<br>- Mm-hmm.
<SYNC Start=3526716><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3526825><P Class=ENCC>
Cool. I've been one time<br>to New York.
<SYNC Start=3529225><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3529327><P Class=ENCC>
Hmm.
<SYNC Start=3531352><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3534499><P Class=ENCC>
Go. Run.
<SYNC Start=3536592><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3536701><P Class=ENCC>
- What do you mean?<br>- Run right now.
<SYNC Start=3538726><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3538837><P Class=ENCC>
This guy has plans for you<br>and your friends...
<SYNC Start=3542136><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3542240><P Class=ENCC>
and his plans are pretty fucking elaborate<br>and pretty fucking fucked.
<SYNC Start=3545141><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3545243><P Class=ENCC>
<i>So if I were you, I'd just run.</i>
<SYNC Start=3547370><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3559324><P Class=ENCC>
Look, we didn't-<br>We're friends of Kiko.
<SYNC Start=3562816><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3562928><P Class=ENCC>
He said- Hey! Shit!
<SYNC Start=3565226><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3568500><P Class=ENCC>
No.
<SYNC Start=3571094><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3586885><P Class=ENCC>
Kiko. Kiko!<br>Where the fuck did you take us?
<SYNC Start=3589786><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3589888><P Class=ENCC>
Tell him we're your friends.<br>Where the fuck are you going?
<SYNC Start=3592686><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3592791><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Kiko!<br>- Tell him we're your friends!</i>
<SYNC Start=3595191><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3595293><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Where are you going?</i>
<SYNC Start=3597386><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3597495><P Class=ENCC>
- Alex, help me!<br>- Hey, hey, hey!
<SYNC Start=3599690><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3599798><P Class=ENCC>
- Get your fucking hands off me!<br>What's the matter with you?
<SYNC Start=3603393><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3603501><P Class=ENCC>
Back off!
<SYNC Start=3605401><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3605503><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, God!
<SYNC Start=3607903><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3660892><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Don't take this personal, okay?</i>
<SYNC Start=3664692><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3668299><P Class=ENCC>
If it makes you feel any better...
<SYNC Start=3670267><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3670368><P Class=ENCC>
please know that I'm doing this...
<SYNC Start=3673201><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3673304><P Class=ENCC>
<i>for a good cause.</i>
<SYNC Start=3676000><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3676107><P Class=ENCC>
Please, don't.
<SYNC Start=3679270><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3679377><P Class=ENCC>
Did you know that in America...
<SYNC Start=3681345><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3681446><P Class=ENCC>
there is a seven-year wait...
<SYNC Start=3684745><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3684849><P Class=ENCC>
for a healthy kidney?
<SYNC Start=3687113><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3689454><P Class=ENCC>
And in Europe...
<SYNC Start=3691081><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3692390><P Class=ENCC>
it's worse.
<SYNC Start=3695086><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3696127><P Class=ENCC>
So...
<SYNC Start=3698027><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3698129><P Class=ENCC>
if a rich gringo needs a kidney...
<SYNC Start=3701189><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3701299><P Class=ENCC>
what does he do?
<SYNC Start=3703267><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3703368><P Class=ENCC>
Wait and get sick and die<br>like the rest of us?
<SYNC Start=3706929><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3707038><P Class=ENCC>
- Don't. Please.<br>- No.
<SYNC Start=3709199><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3711209><P Class=ENCC>
He comes here to Brazil...
<SYNC Start=3713234><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3713344><P Class=ENCC>
to take advantage of our bounty...
<SYNC Start=3715642><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3715747><P Class=ENCC>
and of our poverty.
<SYNC Start=3719979><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3720085><P Class=ENCC>
<i>The whole history of our country...</i>
<SYNC Start=3723486><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3723588><P Class=ENCC>
is you taking from us...
<SYNC Start=3726250><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3726357><P Class=ENCC>
and our land-
<SYNC Start=3728518><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3729561><P Class=ENCC>
rubber, sugar, gold.
<SYNC Start=3731495><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3734432><P Class=ENCC>
And from our bodies-<br>for slaves, for sex.
<SYNC Start=3738095><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3738203><P Class=ENCC>
And now, for- for our insides.
<SYNC Start=3743163><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3749914><P Class=ENCC>
<i>But I...</i>
<SYNC Start=3752144><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3752250><P Class=ENCC>
have had...
<SYNC Start=3754616><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3754719><P Class=ENCC>
enough.
<SYNC Start=3757347><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3808439><P Class=ENCC>
Bea! Bea!
<SYNC Start=3810737><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3811776><P Class=ENCC>
Take the knife!<br>Take it!
<SYNC Start=3814677><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3814779><P Class=ENCC>
Take the knife.<br>Cut this rope off.
<SYNC Start=3817145><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3817248><P Class=ENCC>
Cut this off my hands.
<SYNC Start=3819216><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3830628><P Class=ENCC>
Cut.
<SYNC Start=3832289><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3838102><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Hurry.<br>Bea, hurry!</i>
<SYNC Start=3840730><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3841840><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Attagirl. Attagirl.</i>
<SYNC Start=3844570><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3845476><P Class=ENCC>
Cut- Cut it.
<SYNC Start=3847205><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3849981><P Class=ENCC>
Hurry!
<SYNC Start=3851812><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3861259><P Class=ENCC>
It sickens my heart,<br>this combination-
<SYNC Start=3864057><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3864162><P Class=ENCC>
- your greed-<br>- Oh, God, no.
<SYNC Start=3866756><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3866865><P Class=ENCC>
and our weakness.
<SYNC Start=3869425><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3871302><P Class=ENCC>
And so I am thinking:
<SYNC Start=3874271><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3874372><P Class=ENCC>
Maybe there is something<br>I can do to even the scales just a little-
<SYNC Start=3879810><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3881880><P Class=ENCC>
to help you find a way...
<SYNC Start=3884007><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3884115><P Class=ENCC>
to give back.
<SYNC Start=3886083><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3918049><P Class=ENCC>
Today I am to take<br>the organs of all of you...
<SYNC Start=3921485><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3921586><P Class=ENCC>
and give them...
<SYNC Start=3924384><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3924489><P Class=ENCC>
to the People's Hospital in Rio.
<SYNC Start=3926787><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3928593><P Class=ENCC>
Counting down from right now,<br>I have-
<SYNC Start=3931653><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3931763><P Class=ENCC>
I have about 12 hours...
<SYNC Start=3934129><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3934232><P Class=ENCC>
to get your liver<br>and your kidneys...
<SYNC Start=3937963><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3938069><P Class=ENCC>
and the liver and kidneys...
<SYNC Start=3940060><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3940171><P Class=ENCC>
<i>of all your fucking amiguinhos...</i>
<SYNC Start=3942162><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3942273><P Class=ENCC>
into that helicopter<br>and back to the city.
<SYNC Start=3946175><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3946277><P Class=ENCC>
I'd take your hearts too,<br>your corneas-
<SYNC Start=3951214><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3951316><P Class=ENCC>
even the skin from your lily-white asses.
<SYNC Start=3954376><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3954485><P Class=ENCC>
But they don't travel too well.
<SYNC Start=3956578><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3960491><P Class=ENCC>
You can only keep a heart<br>outside a body for six hours.
<SYNC Start=3964791><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3966597><P Class=ENCC>
But I want that.
<SYNC Start=3968724><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3970001><P Class=ENCC>
I want a heart-
<SYNC Start=3972026><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3973237><P Class=ENCC>
a heart of some<br>arrogant fucking gringo tourist...
<SYNC Start=3976570><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3976674><P Class=ENCC>
pumping life back into the veins...
<SYNC Start=3978665><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3978776><P Class=ENCC>
<i>of a little Brasileiro.</i>
<SYNC Start=3981074><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=3984349><P Class=ENCC>
But that's gonna take more planning.
<SYNC Start=3987443><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4005536><P Class=ENCC>
Your turn.
<SYNC Start=4007936><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4100231><P Class=ENCC>
Come on. Let's go.<br>Come on, come on!
<SYNC Start=4103166><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4103267><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Kiko, grab the key!</i>
<SYNC Start=4105235><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4107238><P Class=ENCC>
Go, go!
<SYNC Start=4109763><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4109874><P Class=ENCC>
- Come on, come on!<br>- Oh, oh!
<SYNC Start=4113275><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4120518><P Class=ENCC>
Hurry up!
<SYNC Start=4122577><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4124889><P Class=ENCC>
Come on, come on!
<SYNC Start=4128416><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4131562><P Class=ENCC>
- Come on. Go to the waterfall.<br>We'll meet you there.<br>- No!
<SYNC Start=4134360><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4134465><P Class=ENCC>
- Alex!<br>- Take her to the waterfall! Go!
<SYNC Start=4136592><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4136701><P Class=ENCC>
- Alex, no!<br>- Come on. Let's get him out.
<SYNC Start=4138760><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4149213><P Class=ENCC>
Please. Please, don't.
<SYNC Start=4151181><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4152984><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Please. Please.</i>
<SYNC Start=4155418><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4162693><P Class=ENCC>
Please don't. Please.
<SYNC Start=4165628><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4165730><P Class=ENCC>
No. No.
<SYNC Start=4169222><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4169333><P Class=ENCC>
No, please don't.
<SYNC Start=4171426><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4171536><P Class=ENCC>
<i>No, please!<br>Please, don't!</i>
<SYNC Start=4173970><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4194959><P Class=ENCC>
Shut up, you-
<SYNC Start=4197359><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4197461><P Class=ENCC>
Come on!
<SYNC Start=4200624><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4200731><P Class=ENCC>
Come on, come on!<br>Let's go!
<SYNC Start=4202995><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4205002><P Class=ENCC>
Come on, come on!<br>Go, go, go, man! Go!
<SYNC Start=4208096><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4208206><P Class=ENCC>
- Come on, come on.<br>- I'm not leaving Finn.
<SYNC Start=4210640><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4210741><P Class=ENCC>
What the fuck you talkin' about?<br>Don't be stupid!
<SYNC Start=4212868><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4212977><P Class=ENCC>
What the fuck is that?<br>Yo, go, man!
<SYNC Start=4214945><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4215046><P Class=ENCC>
- Get the fuck away from me, Kiko!<br>- Ow!
<SYNC Start=4217571><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4280311><P Class=ENCC>
Shh. Stay back.
<SYNC Start=4284407><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4313744><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Jesus, please!<br>Come on now. Go! Go, go!</i>
<SYNC Start=4317578><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4327858><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, fuck.
<SYNC Start=4329985><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4330094><P Class=ENCC>
Come on. I'm gonna get you<br>out of here, bro.
<SYNC Start=4332494><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4332596><P Class=ENCC>
You'll be all right, okay?
<SYNC Start=4335394><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4335499><P Class=ENCC>
Help me get him out.
<SYNC Start=4337626><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4368265><P Class=ENCC>
Fuck! Hurry up! Hurry up!
<SYNC Start=4370859><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4370968><P Class=ENCC>
Come on! Come on!
<SYNC Start=4373198><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4377475><P Class=ENCC>
Quick, quick!
<SYNC Start=4380308><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4390154><P Class=ENCC>
Shh.
<SYNC Start=4392645><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4445776><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Shh. Keep quiet.</i>
<SYNC Start=4448267><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4448379><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Shh!</i>
<SYNC Start=4450711><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4466831><P Class=ENCC>
Let's go. All right,<br>go, go, go, man, go!
<SYNC Start=4468958><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4473471><P Class=ENCC>
Go! Go! Run! Run!
<SYNC Start=4477100><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4483247><P Class=ENCC>
Hey!
<SYNC Start=4485909><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4486016><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, my God. Come on! He's dead!<br>Let's go! Let's go!
<SYNC Start=4490248><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4490354><P Class=ENCC>
Jesus! Come on!
<SYNC Start=4492788><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4492890><P Class=ENCC>
<i>You're crazy! You're crazy!<br>You stupid son of a bitch! What are you doin'?</i>
<SYNC Start=4496758><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4496861><P Class=ENCC>
Fuck you!
<SYNC Start=4499261><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4582646><P Class=ENCC>
- Oh, goddamn it!<br>- Alex! Alex!
<SYNC Start=4585376><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4585482><P Class=ENCC>
Hi.
<SYNC Start=4587848><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4590854><P Class=ENCC>
Hi.
<SYNC Start=4592845><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4595259><P Class=ENCC>
- Amy-Amy's-<br>- No, no, she's gone.
<SYNC Start=4599127><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4599229><P Class=ENCC>
I'm sorry.
<SYNC Start=4601197><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4601298><P Class=ENCC>
Hey, man.
<SYNC Start=4603562><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4604935><P Class=ENCC>
It's danger. Danger, okay?<br>Let's go.
<SYNC Start=4607733><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4607838><P Class=ENCC>
All right.<br>Come on, Bea. Up, up.
<SYNC Start=4609999><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4610107><P Class=ENCC>
- Let's go.<br>- Come on, come on. Let's go.
<SYNC Start=4614009><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4633364><P Class=ENCC>
Hurry, Bea.<br>Come on, come on!
<SYNC Start=4636561><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4646310><P Class=ENCC>
Hey, guys, come on!
<SYNC Start=4648278><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4670668><P Class=ENCC>
You okay?
<SYNC Start=4672659><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4672770><P Class=ENCC>
I've been here most of the night.
<SYNC Start=4675102><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4675205><P Class=ENCC>
What about the others?
<SYNC Start=4677173><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4678676><P Class=ENCC>
They're gone.<br>Come on. We gotta go.
<SYNC Start=4681975><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4682079><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Be quiet! Silence!</i>
<SYNC Start=4684775><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4747478><P Class=ENCC>
- Stop it!<br>- You crazy, man!
<SYNC Start=4751073><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4751181><P Class=ENCC>
This is all your fault! You brought us here!<br>You knew this was gonna happen!
<SYNC Start=4754344><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4754451><P Class=ENCC>
- He's risking his life!<br>- Fuck that!
<SYNC Start=4756681><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4761125><P Class=ENCC>
Go, go, go! Get down! Dive!
<SYNC Start=4763821><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4766797><P Class=ENCC>
Come with me.
<SYNC Start=4769823><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4821552><P Class=ENCC>
- You okay?<br>- What are we gonna do?
<SYNC Start=4824646><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4824755><P Class=ENCC>
We gotta find a way out of here.
<SYNC Start=4827781><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4837067><P Class=ENCC>
- There's someone coming.<br>- What? Who?
<SYNC Start=4839262><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4839369><P Class=ENCC>
<i>I'll find another way out.<br>Follow me.</i>
<SYNC Start=4842236><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4878876><P Class=ENCC>
Turn off your light.
<SYNC Start=4880844><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4885883><P Class=ENCC>
- He's coming! Let's go!<br>- No, I can't! I can't go!
<SYNC Start=4888681><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4888785><P Class=ENCC>
Bea, you have to!<br>Come on!
<SYNC Start=4891117><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4954885><P Class=ENCC>
- Where's Bea?<br>- I don't know.
<SYNC Start=4957012><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=4957120><P Class=ENCC>
Bea.
<SYNC Start=4959020><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5052249><P Class=ENCC>
Bea!
<SYNC Start=5054683><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5115178><P Class=ENCC>
Bea!
<SYNC Start=5117669><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5118782><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Bea!</i>
<SYNC Start=5120750><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5123653><P Class=ENCC>
You okay?
<SYNC Start=5126383><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5126490><P Class=ENCC>
Never leave me again.
<SYNC Start=5128458><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5130727><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Over here. Just take my hand. Come on.</i>
<SYNC Start=5133924><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5134030><P Class=ENCC>
There's land.<br>We can get out here.
<SYNC Start=5136328><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5136433><P Class=ENCC>
- There's an airway up here.<br>- That's great.
<SYNC Start=5139994><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5140103><P Class=ENCC>
This might be the way out.
<SYNC Start=5142901><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5146877><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Let me see it.</i>
<SYNC Start=5149311><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5149412><P Class=ENCC>
It's fine.<br>Here, hold this.
<SYNC Start=5151744><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5156386><P Class=ENCC>
It's fine. It's fine.<br>Let's just find our way out of here.
<SYNC Start=5159321><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5159422><P Class=ENCC>
- We should just keep heading up.<br>- All right.
<SYNC Start=5162152><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5162259><P Class=ENCC>
Let's go.
<SYNC Start=5164420><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5167864><P Class=ENCC>
Alex, get down.
<SYNC Start=5171061><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5172202><P Class=ENCC>
Turn off your light.
<SYNC Start=5174329><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5196393><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Shh, shh, shh. Don't fucking move.</i>
<SYNC Start=5198918><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5211541><P Class=ENCC>
Hey.
<SYNC Start=5215341><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5247744><P Class=ENCC>
<i>Alex! Alex, what are you doing?<br>Get off him!</i>
<SYNC Start=5251578><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5251681><P Class=ENCC>
Stop do-Alex!<br>What are you doing?
<SYNC Start=5254741><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5255952><P Class=ENCC>
Oh! Oh, God.
<SYNC Start=5258546><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5258655><P Class=ENCC>
Oh, my God.
<SYNC Start=5261249><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5275639><P Class=ENCC>
What?
<SYNC Start=5277402><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5411207><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- This is stupid.<br>Why don't we just take the bus?<br>- The bus.</i>
<SYNC Start=5415200><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5415311><P Class=ENCC>
- We could take the bus.<br>Then we could see the country.<br>- The bus takes forever.
<SYNC Start=5418303><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5418415><P Class=ENCC>
- I thought that's why we came<br>here, to experience new things.<br>- Yeah, I guess.
<SYNC Start=5422511><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5422619><P Class=ENCC>
- Take the plane.<br>- What?
<SYNC Start=5424849><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5424954><P Class=ENCC>
Take the plane.
<SYNC Start=5427115><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp
<SYNC Start=5427223><P Class=ENCC>
<i>- Thanks, man.<br>- De nada.</i>
<SYNC Start=5430021><P Class=ENCC>&nbsp

</BODY>
</SAMI>
